David S. Kong: Well… Alright, friends.
David S. Kong: Let us begin.
David S. Kong: We start this campaign, and we start this adventure together.
David S. Kong: In a place that… The four of you know well, the circular island.
David S. Kong: Which is… For purposes of today, and for the next sessions,
David S. Kong: Part of an endless sea, stretching out.
David S. Kong: As far as the eye and the mind can see.
David S. Kong: And this island, perfectly circular, dotted with 8 immense statues.
David S. Kong: And these statues… each representing a…
David S. Kong: Different divine entity, from times long lost.
David S. Kong: And for you all, and for Dragonettes, these names are lost and meaningless, but…
David S. Kong: Once upon a time, they were called the Mother, the Father, the Night Queen, the Warlord, the Sybil.
David S. Kong: The Wanderer, the worldling, and the Wildling.
David S. Kong: But… For you all, as Dragonettes and as part of a very, very special and beautiful community.
David S. Kong: Each of these 8 statues represents home, represents culture, represents community.
David S. Kong: And as we begin, each of these 8 statues, which in Dragonette parlance have actually different names, the mother is known as the Moon Lady.
David S. Kong: The father is known as Brightface.
David S. Kong: The Night Queen is known as the Dark Lady. The Warlord is Old Iron.
David S. Kong: The Sybil is the pretty one.
David S. Kong: The Wanderer is still the wanderer.
David S. Kong: The worldling is crooked luck.
David S. Kong: And the wildling is the tangle.
David S. Kong: Each of these immense statues is home for a different Dragonette community.
David S. Kong: And each of these communities, over time have developed and evolved their own weird little cultures with their own idiosyncrasies and their own passions and knacks and weird little things that happen in their own spaces.
David S. Kong: And each of these statues is literal, physical home for many dragonettes.
David S. Kong: Depending on the statue, some dragonettes are nestled within the cracked and broken robes of the Dark Lady. Some are nestled within the footstructures of Old Iron. Each dragonette
David S. Kong: community finding its own way to work with the large statue and the stone to then find their own nests where clutches of dragonette eggs can be hatched and cared for and loved.
David S. Kong: And where, or also crucially, incredible fun can be had, games can be played, and, bright and generous and kind lives can be lived.
David S. Kong: And so… Today, and we begin this, this, moment first, not…
David S. Kong: attached to what soon will be a very important event in the Dragonet calendar, which is The Dragonhead Festival.
David S. Kong: I'm called the Jubilee.
David S. Kong: Which takes over the entire island, and happens once per year, and is the major, major gathering and moment and celebration for the entire Dragon Antet community, where all of the great
David S. Kong: communities of the Dragonettes, the eight communities gather and, celebrate the great games, the sing-offs, the call-and-responses, the great finds, all of the incredible games that everybody's been looking forward to playing all year.
David S. Kong: But before we bring into that,
David S. Kong: I'd like to bring us into the four characters, the four dragonettes that are, gonna be the heroes and the main characters of our story here.
David S. Kong: Peska.
David S. Kong: and Little Tony, and Sculpit, and Zeno. And I'd like to first bring us into one of the very, very special places
David S. Kong: Certainly for a little Tony and Sculpit.
David S. Kong: And for Little Tony and Sculpit, one of the most
David S. Kong: Important places to the both of them.
David S. Kong: is a very, very special part of the Wanderer statue.
David S. Kong: And up high, high above the clouds, the wanderer's hand and palm is reached out, out into the horizon.
David S. Kong: A symbol for adventure, for journeying, for welcoming the unknown.
David S. Kong: And… Silly.
David S. Kong: Listen.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): So cool!
David S. Kong: And so, I'd like to begin with, sculpit and Little Tony.
David S. Kong: For…
Eric Rosenbaum: Put him in the hand.
David S. Kong: What's that?
Eric Rosenbaum: You could put them in the hand.
David S. Kong: Dude, this is the powers that are possible.
David S. Kong: There they are.
David S. Kong: So, I'd like to begin, first with, Sculpt It and Little Tony.
David S. Kong: Whichever one of you would like to go first. But to share, about your character, and anything you'd like to share about your character, actually, this can be sort of a god view, omnipotent view of your character, and anything about them that, just from a third-person narrative perspective, we can all learn. But then also tell us about this poem.
David S. Kong: And why is this space so important, to you individually, but then also for the two of you together in your friendship?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Do you want to go first? Should I jump in?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): So… Little Tony moves through the island.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Surrounded everywhere he goes by stuff that talks to him.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Not in, like, An ethereal, mystical, beautiful way.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): But in the way that, like, that rock has problems, and it wants to tell Little Tony about its problems that it has, and this stick over here is actually part of the elaborate community of all of the sticks that have washed up on shore.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): and has a long-running feud with the driftwood that comes from outside of the island. And all of them, because…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): There aren't any other Dragonettes that speak with things like this.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): All of them just want to unburden themselves all the time to little Tony.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): It's really frustrating. Like…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): he's a druid, and his former familiar, who is now his ex-familiar, Glenda the Seagull, like, fell in love with him, and he had to convince her.
Eric Rosenbaum: Here.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That he was not going to be in a relationship with a seagull, and now… and this is what he's up in the hand talking about today, is he's updating
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Because he also doesn't want to let her down, like, you know, it's… he feels positively towards this ex, so, like, there's an increasingly elaborate deception about the girlfriend that he's currently in a relationship with, so as to let the seagull down gently. Who isn't his familiar anymore, but…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): comes from time to time. And he's sort of roped Heska into this. Even though Heska doesn't actually talk to the seagull.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): When Tony's talking to the seagull, he needs to look over to Heska from…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Wait, fruit.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Paul said. Say?
Mike: My character's Sculpit.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh, sorry, Sculpit. He needs to, like… Sculpit needs to collaborate and, like, nod at the right times and things, so, like, Tony's running him through the paces.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And,
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): you know, so little Tony is still, like, very much into the celebration and, like, the Dragonite culture and world and everything, and, like.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): He doesn't compete in the performances so much as, like.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): through his network of contacts, like his buddy Horseshoe Crab, who runs the tide pools, like, he finds interesting and unusual things, you know, to sort of bring and display and show off, or in this case.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Helping out, Skopit, who is… he admires as, like, a very talented.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): You know, like, like, coach and choreographer and, and runner of performers.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And he's up in the hand, because this is one of the very, very few places, I think this is the only place he's found on the island, where nothing talks to him.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Like, even though there's, like, trees and plants and moss and rocks and things, like.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): They're all just quiet, and sometimes he needs to just get away from all of the issues.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): So it's good to be up here.
David S. Kong: Schwartz, just as a side note, the one other place that you also, find that.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The voice.
David S. Kong: in your head stop is if you fly out over the ocean and you get close to the storm that surrounds the island.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: But…
David S. Kong: who goes and flies out there on the regular, but you've noticed… Yeah.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): There's also the problem, like, there is this cloud that whenever it sees me get too far, like, just has an infra- like, it thinks I am wasting my life, and just won't stop sometimes.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): She's like, don't go farther than me!
Eric Rosenbaum: Road.
David S. Kong: But on the very few times that you've ever ventured out there, you've noticed also that it gets quiet.
David S. Kong: When you get closer to the storm.
David S. Kong: Shout out to little Tony.
David S. Kong: Sculpt it.
Mike: Don't sculpits!
Mike: up in the… in the hand listening, which is, welcoming little Tony into this place is not something that happens
Mike: in one day. Sculpit is…
Eric Rosenbaum: Bye-bye.
Mike: Behind-the-scenes guy, the creative director and coach and…
Mike: Eater and tougher. He likes making other people better.
Mike: But doesn't like the spotlight himself.
Mike: He's very much the guy who… Who is, you know, On the edge, giving somebody…
Mike: Some good advice on how to make the performance better, not performing himself.
Mike: And he loves the sort of performance culture of the, of the… the islands, but…
Mike: And he… but he often feels disconnected from the sill and bustle of the daily Dragonf life. Like, other than, like, when everybody's cheering for an amazing singer or something like that, he kind of feels that… he feels part of that community, but a lot of the time.
Mike: He feels like everybody's always showing off and being, like, buoyant, and he's kind of quiet and in the background much more.
Mike: And so he comes up to this hand, this place up here, to think and plan out his next, sort of, the choreographic routine for his current
Mike: His current,
Mike: people's not the right word, but… but the person he's currently coaching, through the… through… through their scenes. And for the longest time, he thought he was the only one who knew of this place.
Mike: And discovering another person up here kind of changed his whole…
Mike: attitude on… well, maybe there are some other Dragonettes who are… who it's like…
Mike: We could form a little community that's not a big group, and like, he's very much…
Mike: now sort of attached to this little place with, another person who listen to. He's… he's nodding along. In his head, he's thinking, where's my sparkly things? Where's my sparkly things? But he's nodding along, and, you know, is supportive of, little Tony's,
Mike: life problems. He sometimes thinks that Little Teddy would just
Mike: was to take some advice from somebody that isn't a rock, or a cloud, or a twig, or a stick. Like, life would be better, but, like, you know, to each their own, right? Like,
Mike: So he's, he's a bar, right? He's,
Mike: knows a lot, right? He has this deep store of… he's always coming up with odd facts, you know, about history, or nature, or…
Mike: things like that. Never quite sure where he gets them from, nobody's quite sure if he's made them up or has some source of knowledge, but he'll sped off, you know, oh, well, sure, this statue used to be called such-and-such, it was built by so-and-so, and whatever, and…
Mike: Maybe it's right, maybe it's wrong. These housekeeping listen.
Mike: Down.
Mike: So that's… that's sculpted. And today, he's kind of in a… in a panic. I don't know how much this is something you're gonna get.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Right?
David S. Kong: You can say a little bit, yeah, go for it.
Mike: But he's in a panic right now, because his star quiet has… Completely forgotten to prepare.
Mike: permission.
Mike: And he has come to Little Tony to put out the call amongst his…
Mike: beasts and creatures and twigs and rocks and crabs and seagulls and whoever else. Let's see what can be found to make this costume a success.
Mike: So he doesn't quite have the patience that he would normally.
David S. Kong: Has the key.
Mike: Just kind of thinking…
Mike: Can we get to my problem? He doesn't say. He's too attuned to say it. He's keeping to listening. He's, like, listening to that moment when you're ready to switch gears away from your problem to his problem.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I think it's, like, a regular thing, like, the update on Glenda the Seagull every week is just, like…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): You gotta get it out. Like, no one else will listen to this.
David S. Kong: So the palm is the source of therapy and, ability for Lil' Tony to… To finally release.
David S. Kong: Beautiful, y'all. Well, and so, we'll come back to the palm in a moment, but now, we're gonna shift scenes and go to…
David S. Kong: The neighborhood and the community of the Dark Lady.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, yeah.
David S. Kong: And so, the Dark Lady, again, each, each Dragonette,
David S. Kong: Community, different, diverse, connected to their own.
David S. Kong: Their own statues.
David S. Kong: Much of the… of the neighborhoods built in the cracks of the robes, and
David S. Kong: Is the home of… of, Heska and Xena.
David S. Kong: Who also are friends and have known each other for quite some time.
David S. Kong: And Zeno and Huska.
David S. Kong: Please introduce yourselves and your relationship.
Eric Rosenbaum: So Zeno, for, like, the 13th time today, is like.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yo. Now I'm back to thinking…
Eric Rosenbaum: The chuck… the chuckle buckle. People would like that, I think, right? Because she has a giant shoe, you know, that thing that holds on the shoe, that… I think, in ancient times, that was called a buckle. And if people want to come out for a show, they're not gonna remember.
Eric Rosenbaum: you know, Dark Lady Night.
Eric Rosenbaum: They know about the Dark Lady.
Eric Rosenbaum: And so, we got, you know… It's gotta pop.
Eric Rosenbaum: It's gotta have some magic to it, if we want people to come to the comedy show.
Eric Rosenbaum: You know what I'm saying?
Eric Rosenbaum: Zeno is trying to get something together.
Eric Rosenbaum: He… he would love to form a crew around him, and get a scene going.
Eric Rosenbaum: With his… based on his spoken word.
Eric Rosenbaum: prowess. But, you know, he's… he's working on it. He is a…
Eric Rosenbaum: Orange dragging it with green highlights. He is,
Eric Rosenbaum: He's got a scarf that he's very proud of that's dotted with…
Eric Rosenbaum: Tiny Gems. You often see them.
Eric Rosenbaum: Just toss it over his shoulder, even though he just did that a few seconds ago, to, like, draw attention to it.
Eric Rosenbaum: And nobody can defeat him.
Eric Rosenbaum: In a battle of wits or words.
Eric Rosenbaum: Or so he thinks.
David S. Kong: And what about your relationship to, to, Tesco?
Eric Rosenbaum: Well, Heska is gonna be the nightclub manager in Zeno's mind. I don't… I don't know if Heska sees that way… sees it that way. Heska might have just stumbled into this by accident.
Eric Rosenbaum: But we do collect, delicious eggs together sometimes.
Tim Sackton: Heska… so… Is patiently listening to…
Tim Sackton: You know, change his mind for probably the 12th time today.
Tim Sackton: About what he wants to call this club, that he's been…
Tim Sackton: Talking about for probably the past 6 months, and has not, in fact, done anything to Establish.
Tim Sackton: But… but Heska is patient, and… and every now and then, you know, hell…
Tim Sackton: try and… try and redirect… redirect Zeno a little bit to some, like…
Tim Sackton: you know, memory back from one of the earlier Jubilees or something, where,
Tim Sackton: Where Zeno was, you know, had some… some big moment or something like that.
Tim Sackton: And… What?
Tim Sackton: Zeno doesn't notice, but what our omniscient third-party observer sees is that when he gets… when he manages to get
Tim Sackton: Zino… talking at length about some fancy memory of Dino's past great triumphs, and most of seen as…
Tim Sackton: Past events are great triumphs.
Tim Sackton: Something will just, you know, a little,
Tim Sackton: handkerchief or something will just, like, lift quietly out of Sina's pocket and, like, drift across the air.
Tim Sackton: And…
Tim Sackton: Zeno never notices, but eventually we'll go to grab his handkerchief, and it's… there's not a handkerchief there anymore. There's a deflating wet balloon, or some such other loud, silly rubber chick… well, it's probably not rubber chickens, but a,
Tim Sackton: Noisy, loud.
Tim Sackton: Maybe an egg.
Eric Rosenbaum: Funny eggshell.
Tim Sackton: A slimy eggshell in his pocket instead.
Tim Sackton: But… but you can tell, you're the omniscient third-party observer, that he does this not out of malice, but out of…
Tim Sackton: A sense of… love for… for Zeno's story, and trying to keep him from Insulating his ego.
Tim Sackton: More than a reasonable size.
David S. Kong: And what is Heska known for on the island?
Tim Sackton: I was gonna prefer not to be known for much, but if you asked somebody.
Tim Sackton: What they would probably describe as a couple times that he has…
Tim Sackton: Flown out over the ocean and brought back something strange and weird for the… Dark Lady communal feasts.
Tim Sackton: The thing people talk about the most is…
Tim Sackton: a giant fiddler crab, twice the size of any dragonette, with a claw nearly the size of Heska's
Tim Sackton: Like, torso and head.
Tim Sackton: Betty brought back and cooked up in a very nice crab boil.
Tim Sackton: But the shell is, like, decorated in this, like, swirling rainbow that looks like crashing waves, and…
Tim Sackton: He keeps promising Zeno, once you finally settle on a name, you can decorate your club with… with the…
Tim Sackton: Giant fiddler crab shell.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yes.
David S. Kong: And this fits in perfectly with some of the larger Dragonhead culture around finding and displaying cool shit.
David S. Kong: And this could be… and this is also why little Tony is so sought after by so many across the island, because of his unusual capacity and ability to find all the cool, strange shit on the island, which maybe is a verdict, maybe it's a source of pride?
David S. Kong: Little Tony, can you say a little more about your relationship to this… this energy on the island, related to your…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Last year, I came in third place in one of the Finding Interesting Thing competitions, because I found a pebble that looked like a butt, and it was… it looked so much like a butt. It was… Pebble butt. And even the people who thought it was ridiculous, and like, this is not an appropriate thing, were like, yeah, but it looks like a butt.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And so yeah, so he, he spends a lot of the time
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Because he has this, like, community of things that talks to him everywhere he goes, you know, he just goes out and spends a lot of time wandering around and…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): talking with inanimate objects and, like, looking for interesting things to find and bring back, so… So sometimes he'll… like, his part in some of the competitions is… is finding that, like, when you want a particular thing, like, little Tony knows a guy who knows a guy, like, who knows a twig, who knows where it is.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And, like, that's the… that's the go-to.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And he likes that, like, he likes finding things for people, and he likes just being out wandering around.
David S. Kong: And just, again, the finding weird shit. There's both the finding weird shit that is, like, strange objects, but there's also…
David S. Kong: hunting things, and being able to feed the community is another incredible source of pride and joy in the Dragon Egg community. And Heska, I know, I know, Heska, you've also, had some expertise in that particular
David S. Kong: Lane. This is something that you're known for a bit.
David S. Kong: Even though you're not known for much, but one of these things is something you're very known for.
Tim Sackton: Huska is… Peska likes to feed the Dark Lady.
Tim Sackton: It's always bringing stuff back, but usually not…
Tim Sackton: not in a way that draws attention to himself, he's actually often happy to let Z know
Tim Sackton: like, it's a… it's a way to, you know, Zeno's doing a show, so… so Heska will cook up something nice and get everybody to come eat.
Tim Sackton: And watch the show.
Eric Rosenbaum: But Zeno's contribution is he's always by Heska's side.
Eric Rosenbaum: Hyping him up while he's hunting.
Tim Sackton: Yes.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, Zeno comes to fly out, and then just flies around. Like, you can kill that thing, you can find it, doesn't actually do anything at all. Heska catches the thing and brings it back. But Heska likes it.
David S. Kong: And what's an example of a thing or two that's, like, an exotic, strange thing or two that you've brought back that perhaps.
Tim Sackton: Well, the most famous is the fiddler crab, as previously described.
Tim Sackton: His favorite thing to do is to steal eggs from the birds that nest on the cliffs and replace them with
Tim Sackton: Egg-sized rocks, which oftentimes the birds are too stupid to realize are not actually their eggs, and will sit on and incubate.
Tim Sackton: Until they get confused.
Tim Sackton: But he only does that occasionally, because he knows if…
Tim Sackton: He just takes the eggs, the birds will usually lay another one, and then that's more food for everybody.
Tim Sackton: But he… he finds it funny.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, that's… that's interesting.
David S. Kong: So…
David S. Kong: all of the four of you, again, you all know… you're all aware of each other, but certainly, Sculpit and Little Tony are… are… are definitely… have a very unique and close friendship, much like,
David S. Kong: Much like, Heska and, Zeno do.
David S. Kong: And that brings us now into, the great festival, the Jubilee, sometimes formally called, what is it formally called?
David S. Kong: Well, Jubilee is what it's most commonly known as, but the Eightfold Festival is often… some of the elders will also refer to it that way.
David S. Kong: And… We bring ourselves into the morning of the festival.
David S. Kong: And the festival itself, kicks off… it's a multi-day affair, and it kicks off, just before sunset with a very important opening ceremony that occurs at sunset. And,
David S. Kong: upon completion of the open ceremony, where the elders will convene and conduct what is overall one of the few moments in Dragonite culture that actually has some solemnity involved.
David S. Kong: Which transitions immediately into, it's kind of like the Olympics starting ceremony. You know, there's a huge set of performances, and those performances then transition into the games. And most importantly for today, and most importantly for Sculpit.
David S. Kong: Sculpit's advisee, Xena, Is… has a critical and major role to play as a part of this opening ceremony.
David S. Kong: The solemnity of the opening with the elders is something that everyone, again, one of the very, very few times in Dragonite culture that everybody takes this real seriously, because, and I'll share more, but it relates to the clutches and the eggs and the families that are born and reborn, throughout the festival time.
David S. Kong: But this particular day and this particular performance, Xena…
David S. Kong: is gonna have a major moment, and Sculptit has been working with Xena behind the scenes for months and months for this big, big, event.
David S. Kong: And so… As we bring ourselves into the morning of the festival, Let's see here…
David S. Kong: As we bring ourselves into the morning of the festival, and the festival itself takes place in the temple that's located at the center of the island. Pilgrimage roads lead from the center all the way out to each of the large eight statues, bright face.
David S. Kong: you know, the wildling, or, the wanderer and beyond. But this morning, what happens is Xena, who is the star of the show.
David S. Kong: She is in a panic. And there's basically, in the main temple area, there's kind of, like, a green room area set over on a side, which is a large cabana area.
David S. Kong: And this is sort of the dry rehearsal period, where everybody that's gonna be doing some kind of performance, you know, the various musicians are, like, have their instruments out, they're all doing their sound checks, everybody's just kind of trying to get ready in advance before everybody shows up. Obviously, this image has got everybody here, but imagine it, you know, like, this is before it all happens.
David S. Kong: And so, we start this scene with, with Sculptit.
David S. Kong: and Xena, but also with,
David S. Kong: with, Lil Tony, who Sculpted has brought by, as a part of this preparation. And Xena is lovely. Xena is such a talent
David S. Kong: an incredible flyer and acrobat, that's part of why she's so famous, but also an incredible vocalist, which is a very, very rare combination. Often in these Dragonet parties and these Dragonet sing-offs and these competitions that happen.
David S. Kong: Usually, it's around one skill, and Zena is a particular talent because she can both, has this incredible body control and dexterity and physical performance, but also can sing.
David S. Kong: And so, Sculpit, you are a little panicked because Xena is doing her usual thing, and she's a bit of a diva, but also completely forgetful, very, very late, and is freaking out. And she's freaking out for a couple of things. She's freaking out because, she doesn't think that her costume is quite right.
David S. Kong: But she's also freaking out because she feels like she needs help.
David S. Kong: From somebody that she has a bit of a crush on, and she's gonna tell you more about that in a moment.
David S. Kong: But, Heska, you and Zeno are also here as a part of this, this opening ceremony.
David S. Kong: prep part. You know, a lot of the dragonettes are just kind of, if you're curious, kind of coming and hanging out. But frankly, a lot of the dragonettes are out preparing their own shit, right? Like, the great find is happening, so everybody's getting, you know, the coolest fucking random, you know, hunt that they've gotten, preparing it in the most beautiful way, for the great hunt. For the great find, all the strange objects are being arrayed and set up in the tents. So this is, like, just pre-party, like, major planning moment.
David S. Kong: And, and so, so, Heskins, you know, you both are nearby, in a nearby tent, just, just hanging out, checking things out, but we start with,
David S. Kong: with Sculptit and with little Tony, and Xena walks up to both of you, and… Xena is, like.
David S. Kong: she, as a dragonette, has got, like, just ripped arms, and, like, her wings are super, super just felt, and she's got this amazing, just, energy about her, but has this huge pot belly. She just has, like, this weird aerodynamic, like, you know, she's got this, like, pot belly, which is tattooed and decorated with jewels, and is bedazzled. But she's also, like.
David S. Kong: This is not enough.
David S. Kong: And sculpt it.
David S. Kong: You said you were gonna bring me some actual jewelry, and this shit does not look good, number one.
David S. Kong: And number two, For my acrobatics, that's gonna happen later.
David S. Kong: You had this choreography for me, but I think it now should be a duet. And I need a duo.
Mike: Rev.
David S. Kong: What?
Mike: Going away, don't you think? We have the… We had this all organized!
Mike: You sure?
David S. Kong: we had this all organized. I feel like you have not been organized at all. I have been ready, and I've been waiting for both… I know I came up with this idea of needing a partner just now, but I feel like
David S. Kong: It's something that you need to be delivering on as my chief advisor.
Mike: I have an idea for apartments.
David S. Kong: Well, let's talk about two things. Let's talk about my outfit, and let's talk about my partner. What's going on with my outfit?
Mike: So remember when I told you that, and he sort of, he allied to what he was gonna say for that, like,
Mike: some things that I told you that we should repeat right back, but did you find anything, that would fit, like I asked?
Mike: So, so, so, can you give us a minute? Little Tony sometimes, like.
Mike: Can you just give it… we'll… we'll be right back.
David S. Kong: Xena is… Xena is, like, staring daggers into both of you, just like, what the fuck is going on? My belly is unadorned, my wings are bare, my scales are, like, a little flaky right now, like…
David S. Kong: What's the situation, you two?
David S. Kong: What's going on here?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): We'll, we'll, we'll… we'll huddle up, and then we'll get back.
David S. Kong: Before you do that, I just want to share one other thing, and also, side note. So, everybody probably is aware of this, because Xena's kind of a big, you know, people know about Xena. Xena and Zeno
David S. Kong: are clutch mates, so they're actually siblings. They were born in the same clutch, and Zeno, part of why you're hanging around nearby this tent is because you know how Xena gets a little bit before these performances.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yes, yes.
David S. Kong: So, and she gets a little edgy, and it's one of those things, you know, you as, you know, her sib and her bro, you've got, like, a little bit of a, you know, you're able to kind of smooth out these swim situations.
David S. Kong: If necessary, so you're kind of just… you're kind of, like, keeping an eye out and just seeing if what the temperature in the tent is, and it's starting to get a little hot. It's starting to get a little hot in the tent.
David S. Kong: So Xena's staring daggers at y'all, and is… and also, kinda…
David S. Kong: What's going on? What are you two doing?
Mike: Wow.
Mike: I pick a… I pick a duet!
Mike: It's a little complicated, but let's deal with the caustic first.
David S. Kong: Let's talk about the costume, you two figure this out. Zeno, come over here.
Eric Rosenbaum: Zeno's little… little wings perk up. He spins around, says, Oh, hello, little sister, you're all… all ready, aren't you?
Eric Rosenbaum: All ready for the show?
David S. Kong: because of these two fools, I'm not.
Eric Rosenbaum: All ready to go, no?
Eric Rosenbaum: Are they working a little too…
Eric Rosenbaum: Slow for ya. You got this.
Eric Rosenbaum: You don't need them.
Eric Rosenbaum: What's the matter?
David S. Kong: Well, I think it's more that I demand a certain level of excellence that is not being delivered right now by my most trusted advisor, so…
Eric Rosenbaum: Well… Did you get it in writing? You could fire them.
David S. Kong: Writing.
David S. Kong: Xeno… I need to confess something to you.
David S. Kong: And Xena kind of, like, gets over and leans over, like, closely and leans into you.
David S. Kong: Is that friend of yours here?
Eric Rosenbaum: Who's that?
David S. Kong: An acrobat, the one that can fly around.
David S. Kong: And hunt stuff.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, I… you mean Heska?
Eric Rosenbaum: You mean Eska? Yeah, he's right over there anymore.
Eric Rosenbaum: What's…
David S. Kong: Ever since he got that crap?
David S. Kong: A little crush on you.
Eric Rosenbaum: Brilliant.
David S. Kong: Dumped down.
Eric Rosenbaum: That crab is something. You know, we got big plans for that crab.
David S. Kong: Yeah, but…
Eric Rosenbaum: Wait, let me tell you, I gotta… I'm trying to decide on the… oh, okay, go ahead.
David S. Kong: It was the crap.
Eric Rosenbaum: What do you think about the… the chuckle Buckle? Or maybe it's the buckle chuckle?
David S. Kong: Yeah, I don't care about any of that. Okay, so look.
David S. Kong: Here's the thing.
David S. Kong: I think what's gonna make this performance really take off
David S. Kong: is if Heska does it with me?
David S. Kong: Know what I mean?
David S. Kong: Like, we do it together.
Eric Rosenbaum: Well… now, Heska's a very, very busy, dragonett, you know.
Eric Rosenbaum: Well, I have to approach this delicately.
David S. Kong: I'm just saying, if that doesn't happen, Xena's gonna have a meltdown.
Eric Rosenbaum: Let's just take a deep breath together. Yeah. And spit some fire, because let's get Huska. Come on.
David S. Kong: Okay, okay, okay.
David S. Kong: Xena, Xena's a perk really distracted right now. What are… Little Tony and Sculptit, what are you doing?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): We're circling, like, I'm scubbing, I'm… I'm sorry, I… I just get really intimidated by a powerful woman. It's hard, like, I… I don't know what's… I… she's… she's so, like, so much, you know?
Mike: She's a lot. Yeah, I don't… I don't really beat this, honestly, I…
Mike: But our performances are quite good. It's kind of nice to… to help, but…
Mike: She takes it too far, you're not wrong.
David S. Kong: Her performances are amazing, like, they're amazing. They are amazing, and Sculpit, you're like, this is like… this is, like, the shit you're putting up with, but also you know she's gonna deliver, but also, it's a lot.
Mike: Did you, did you find anything interesting out, out of Monster Prize?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I mean…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): He pulls the bag off his waist, and pours several pebbles that appear indistinguishable to you, and begins to explain the differences, the very, very subtle differences that
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That really makes this, like, the connoisseurs. This is, like, this is really the pebble collector's pebble. Like, among the pebble community, this is the… like.
Eric Rosenbaum: For the general public.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Public, not as much, but, like, if you're a pebblehead, man, like, oh, shit.
Eric Rosenbaum: So…
Mike: No, I think the… I think the rectum was just… just a tiny bit more in the direction of, like, noticeable, sparkly things that we could see from far away.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah…
Mike: I get where you're coming from. I mean, don't get me wrong, I appreciate the pebble as much as…
Mike: That's some people, I guess. I… I haven't met them, but,
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Hmm.
Mike: But these aren't quite what we're, what we're.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I appreciate the note, no, no, these are good notes, I appreciate the notes, like, I'm… I'm taking… I'm taking them seriously.
Mike: You gotta put your mind in the mind of the audience.
Mike: Not yourself, like, take a step out of yourself.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I just… I get flustered, because, like, she's really hot when she bullies you, you know? Like, I mean, no, sure, I mean,
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yes, we can find it. We can find it, is what I'm saying.
Mike: That's what I talked to you before, right? Like, like, I, I, I…
Mike: Nope, you did well, you did well.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Okay, okay, okay, he pulls out a handkerchief and is mobbing the sweat. Okay, we can figure this out. We can figure this out. So, jewelry, sparkly, yes. Yes.
David S. Kong: And you have time, you have time. Like, it's like 5 hours. The actual performance is like 5 hours. You got a little… there's a little bit of time. Something like…
Mike: Like, visible, right? That'll make a statement.
Mike: like, a statement piece, but, like, the statement is, I'm beautiful, and powerful, and amazing.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): No, I mean, I heard that statement. Like, I…
Mike: But…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I couldn't hear anything else, like…
Mike: So just remember that, and we're not sort of going after the statement of, I'm interested in wrongs.
Mike: That's a perfectly valid statement. I get it. I totally get it.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): No, respect… I'm… okay, okay, I'm locked in, I'm locked in. Yep.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): We're gonna figure this out.
David S. Kong: Xena, upon hearing that, like, the beautiful… she, like, kind of turns her and is like.
David S. Kong: So what are you gonna do to make me beautiful?
Mike: We're working on it, right? You know this takes time.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Mike: Right? We've done this before. This is not our first time.
David S. Kong: It's not. It's not. It's not. And Xena…
Mike: No, it'll work.
David S. Kong: Xena's patient. Xena's patient.
David S. Kong: But also, Xena is gonna kill you if you don't deliver.
David S. Kong: So, Lil Tony, just whatever you're experiencing right now, it's like, it's like, the I'm gonna kill you is, like, is, like, pretty, it's, it's pretty intense. It's pretty intense. So…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Little Tony crosses his legs.
Mike: You know, we've talked about that kind of language.
David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: Moving on, I trust you, I'mma give it some time, you all go… do what you have to do, and let's see if we can deliver.
David S. Kong: Very important thing to talk about with you
David S. Kong: sculpt it about this duo that I think needs to happen now, because I woke up this morning, and I had a vision of myself and another dragonette.
David S. Kong: It has incredible flying prowess doing this with me.
David S. Kong: And I have an idea, and she just, like, Zeno, she just, like, pulls you in, you know, and just, like… and… this is my brother, you know Zeno.
David S. Kong: Zeno is gonna help.
David S. Kong: Because… he thinks…
David S. Kong: that the best partner for me for this situation is Heska. And I did not think that was a great idea. I said that that's not smart.
David S. Kong: Because Heska, you know, he's all this hunter guy, mysterious and everybody. But, I agreed after he begged me. He begged me and said.
David S. Kong: Like, he was gonna denounce me as a sister if I didn't do it. So, because of the begging, I said.
David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: I will do it, but only without.
Mike: That's it.
David S. Kong: So, Sculptit, this is…
David S. Kong: I know, I know that you're the advisor, and that I know that the goal here is for me to listen to your advice, but in this situation, it's more like, you're gonna do exactly what I say, and that is we're gonna have Heska be my partner.
David S. Kong: What do you think about that?
Mike: Wow.
Mike: Think we could make it work.
Mike: I can…
David S. Kong: I need more confidence. I need more confidence from you.
Mike: Wow!
Mike: Really, your confidence matters a lot more than anybody else's.
Mike: Cause, cause you're the one who makes the show.
Mike: Powerful and villiant, right?
Mike: It's more about… it's more about…
Mike: We've talked about it. It's more about you claiming your place In the performance.
David S. Kong: You're right!
Mike: Than it is about anybody else.
David S. Kong: You're right.
Mike: Right? So have faith in yourself.
David S. Kong: Right.
Mike: right?
Mike: It'll be right.
David S. Kong: Okay? I hear that.
Mike: make it work.
David S. Kong: But what is the role Heska is playing in this? Because the Heska duet thing, I think… I think now that's part of the vision, so what's… what do you think?
David S. Kong: Zeno, I see him, Zeno, Zeno, I see him over there, just bring him over, just get him.
Mike: So…
David S. Kong: Zeno… Heska!
Eric Rosenbaum: Maybe we… Esca about it.
Tim Sackton: Haska has been sitting in the tent that…
Tim Sackton: that him and Zeno were talking on, and he's,
Tim Sackton: he's… he's, like, just fiddling with some… I don't know, a pair of dice or something, just kind of, like…
Tim Sackton: you know, tossing them around in his hand, doing little dice tricks and things like that. Not really paying too much attention to the, to, to the conversation, but when,
Tim Sackton: Xena, is that her name? Xena shouts Heska. He, like, looks over quickly, sees who's shouting his name, and then, like, drops the dice awkwardly, and, ducks behind the bench.
David S. Kong: Oh, I saw that! Heska!
David S. Kong: I saw that. You can't hide from me.
Mike: Tina, Tina?
Eric Rosenbaum: And Xena strolls over.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah, yeah, let's…
Mike: October, okay?
David S. Kong: Let's go talk.
Mike: No, no, not… No, no, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Tim Sackton: Dino gets over it, he says.
Mike: Thank you.
Tim Sackton: the sense.
Mike: I'll be back. Just, just stay here.
David S. Kong: You want me to stay here, sculpt? Yes. Okay, fine, fine.
Mike: Take it.
David S. Kong: I stay, I stay here.
Mike: Right? Stop it, I'll swallow.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Don't leave me here with her!
David S. Kong: Mike, really quick, adjust your audio, it's, like, very muffled, your audio is, like, like… Yeah, yeah.
Mike: Sorry, I didn't matter.
David S. Kong: No, you're good, you're good. This is…
Tim Sackton: Why is she shouting my name?
Mike: So…
Eric Rosenbaum: It's cool, man. How do you think… how high do you think you could throw something the size of Xena?
Eric Rosenbaum: She's, like, kind of medium-sized, right? Like, you could probably…
Eric Rosenbaum: Like, launch her straight up in the air.
Eric Rosenbaum: You've done that before.
Eric Rosenbaum: Or, like, what if you were swinging her by your legs? That'd be… that'd be fine, right?
Eric Rosenbaum: Have you done this before, right? Haven't you?
Mike: Sorry, Nito, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Mike: These sound like terrible ideas.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Wait, wait.
Tim Sackton: Wait, wait, wait.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): You should listen to him.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): about.
Mike: Okay, so there's an opportunity here, Heska. So, I don't think we… have we… Have we met?
Tim Sackton: Have we met?
David S. Kong: Yeah, you're all aware of each other, you're just…
Mike: Yeah.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, but, like, we don't know each other.
Mike: Yeah, yeah, yeah. So… We've had an artistic vision.
Mike: Right? That we'd like you to be part of.
Mike: Not… I don't know what your friend is. I think he's a…
Mike: have a different kind of vision that I'd rather look at some point.
Mike: But… but Zena and I have had an artistic vision, like, I really think… Have you?
Mike: Hasco's not really… participating, like, you're mostly a hunter, right?
Tim Sackton: Yeah, he's never participated in… Pascal's never performed a solo… as far as you know, has never performed a solo.
Mike: Now.
Tim Sackton: locked in anything.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Let me put it a different way. Have you smelled her? She smelled so good!
Tim Sackton: He kind of laughs nervously.
Eric Rosenbaum: I don't know if we should be talking about my sister this way, but she is very skilled.
Eric Rosenbaum: No, no.
Mike: Some of us care.
Mike: It's more about the games that all this nonsense you folks are talking about.
Mike: Look, we have a sacred duty here to…
Tim Sackton: Right?
Mike: these games.
Mike: And make these performances.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That's right.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): What's up?
Mike: powerful and, and, and… as… football as we possibly can.
Eric Rosenbaum: And this is what I'm talking about. Heska is a strong and brave and powerful hunter.
Mike: Cassidy.
Eric Rosenbaum: Who could probably…
Mike: Let's…
Tim Sackton: No, I… no, no, too many peop… I don't perform in front of people.
Mike: No, no, we didn'.
Eric Rosenbaum: You're not performing, you're just gonna…
Mike: You know, you know.
Eric Rosenbaum: Support.
Mike: Yeah, wait.
Mike: Let's just go… I'd love to see me fly. I've never really watched him fly.
Mike: Right? You're a hunter. You must be good, okay?
Tim Sackton: Good at hunting?
Mike: Isn't flying the biggest part of hunting?
Tim Sackton: You'd be surprised.
Mike: Well, I… look, I'd love to see it. Can you… can you… Yeah,
Mike: Tell you what, give me a minute,
Eric Rosenbaum: Just throw anything up in the air, he'll catch it.
Mike: There we go. Yeah, he starts… he starts muttering.
Mike: Give me… give me a few minutes here. Yeah, let's… let's…
Mike: Let's… let's go somewhere where it's a little less crap.
Mike: Right? Like, there's a few people around here, like, like, will you come with me for a minute?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): You're gonna wanna see my boy work. Mmm.
Tim Sackton: Aska looks over at Little Tony, who… Little Tony has probably, like, talked to a few times, just because they both tend to wander around weird places on the island.
Tim Sackton: For different reasons, this is all very strange.
Tim Sackton: Okay.
Tim Sackton: I'll go where there's fewer people.
Mike: Alright, let's go.
Tim Sackton: So…
Mike: We… as we're watching.
Tim Sackton: You know, you're coming, yeah?
Tim Sackton: Leave me with them by myself.
Eric Rosenbaum: I… I don't know what he's up to, actually, I'll go with you, yeah.
David S. Kong: So, right now, right now, Xena, Xena is just with, with Lil' Tony.
Mike: No, no, little Tony.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): No, no, no, little Tony.
Tim Sackton: Bill Tony was scared and went out of the tent.
Mike: If you're gonna do it, don't.
David S. Kong: Xena's like, okay, you all can leave.
David S. Kong: But if you're not back in, like, 3 minutes.
Mike: Go up and walk back over. This is… remember. Yes. Everybody… everybody needs to feed their skills in a small place.
Mike: Yeah. We gotta see what he does before we plan to…
David S. Kong: Okay, okay, but we all know. But he's cute!
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Little Tony calls out with a very low level of self-confidence, trust the process!
Mike: Okay.
Mike: like… The performance is what matters to you.
David S. Kong: Make it happen.
Mike: You gotta trust me, you gotta trust…
David S. Kong: I trust you. I trusted…
Mike: orbits.
David S. Kong: I trust the process, I trust little Tony's gonna find the things that need to be found.
David S. Kong: She doesn't…
Mike: app.
David S. Kong: Bids back.
David S. Kong: Into the tents.
Mike: So, somehow.
David S. Kong: Patience.
Mike: As you're… as we're walking,
Mike: or flying, or whatever.
Mike: So, if it's kind of muttering and kind of waving his hands a little bit.
Mike: And… I, you know, he, he…
Mike: about a few minutes, we get somewhere a little bit more quiet, right? And he takes,
Mike: color… something out of a little pouch or something, enhance it to. Apparently, the thin air, where there's now…
Mike: He's cast some sort of spell.
Mike: And sends, it says, here, show me, chase that!
Mike: And, some invisible creature holding, a little ball, or…
Mike: You know, clot or something, some bread thing, starts running off the other church.
Eric Rosenbaum: It's an interesting pebble.
Mike: Like, I just want to see you fly and hunt. That's just something to hunt, let's see how it goes.
Tim Sackton: Make a persuasion check.
David S. Kong: I like it.
Eric Rosenbaum: Who's the DM?
David S. Kong: Thank you, Tim. Thank you, Tim.
Mike: WP6.
Eric Rosenbaum: Barry, what did you call?
Mike: I rolled a 19, and I have a plus 7.
David S. Kong: Hell yeah.
Tim Sackton: Hey, Lux!
Tim Sackton: I'm sort of curious and interested in this thing, and takes a running leap into the air.
Tim Sackton: And as he does.
Tim Sackton: He has a whip coiled on his back that he, like, takes out of his cloak, and he's, like, holding this whip as he flies into the air, and he, like, cracks it. Like, it's… the reach of the whip is, like, as long as he is, so it's, like, 10 feet long. Ahead of him into the air.
David S. Kong: Wait, Tim, make an acrobatics check?
Tim Sackton: 11.
David S. Kong: -Oh.
Tim Sackton: But misses, and throws his balance off, tumbling slightly into the, air, and sort of dives awkwardly, catching the,
Tim Sackton: The… the thing with…
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh…
Mike: Wow.
Tim Sackton: I was awkwardly catching the ball with his… with his claw, having missed it with his lip.
Mike: So…
Tim Sackton: Holds it up. Still got it.
Mike: Yeah? Get what you did there? Right?
Mike: I think we can incorporate this.
Mike: We're gonna try it again. Here's a few pointers. Small bit will give.
Mike: some fairly perceptive pointers on how to be better than we just did. Like, I don't know what they would be, like, I don't know how to be.
David S. Kong: Fair pointers. It's got the eye.
Mike: Great pointers, right? I think you should try again, right? Like, my whole thing is, like, you get advantage, you can try again, right?
Tim Sackton: Right.
Mike: I think you should try again. I think, I think, I think the width… could work well.
Mike: I think we… we need to come up with a way of incorporating this into… into… it seems thematic for you. I don't want to take the thematic bit away.
Mike: And I think… It takes a little bit of,
Mike: Friction and a little bit of danger might go well for,
Mike: for Zena. She might appreciate. So, like, let's… let's play that up a bit, as, you know, a little bit of a…
Mike: a talent on your side, okay? So, like…
Mike: Let's try again. I really think that you're much better than you think you are.
Mike: Okay? I think if you just take a little bit of advice, and you try a few more times, you'll find that actually, you really could get up to…
Mike: Close to her level.
Mike: And it would be really good for you, I think, to be seen more, right? Like, doesn't everybody want to be seen in a performance?
Mike: He says, guy, Clark's a little bit.
Tim Sackton: Huska's kind of, like, shaking his head, but is swept up a little bit by,
Tim Sackton: Stop it's like… Patter and… and vibe and…
Tim Sackton: Very high persuasion role, and
Tim Sackton: caught in… caught into the flow a little bit. And…
Tim Sackton: Just kind of finds himself leaping forward, rolling again.
David S. Kong: With Advantage.
David S. Kong: Acrobatics check with advantage.
Tim Sackton: Yep.
Tim Sackton: That is a 22.
David S. Kong: Woo! Alright.
Mike: I knew you were… yeah, I knew you were getting.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): elbows, you know, and the ribs, like, I told you my boy can't cook!
Tim Sackton: So… so, I mean, what he was trying to do before works this time, where he leaps into the air chasing after this magically dancing
Tim Sackton: ball, and, dives… flies up above it, and begins to dive down, like, swinging the whip
Tim Sackton: around his head in the air, and then cracks it, and this time, instead of missing and him crashing into the ball, it catches directly on the ball, and he flips the whip. I don't know what spell you're using, but presumably you can…
Tim Sackton: Okay. He pulls it out of the Unseen servant's hand, flips it into the air, and then just reaches up and catches it with his hand as he…
Tim Sackton: Lands on the ground.
Eric Rosenbaum: Nice.
David S. Kong: as he lands, as he lands, you hear, just kind of, like, bursting from the bushes, like, Xena has been, like, hiding and watching this whole time, and she, like, falls over and is like.
David S. Kong: That was so hot.
Tim Sackton: He's like…
David S. Kong: Yeah, it has LA.
Tim Sackton: So, Heska is normally, like, a green-scale dragonette with, like, silver…
Tim Sackton: highlights, and silver eyes, and all the little silver bits turn red. He looks like a Christmas tree.
David S. Kong: Xena, like, flies over, and is, like, gets in, like, Heska's, like, very close proximity, and is like, Heska, you need to do that, and we're gonna do that together, tonight, in front of everybody.
Tim Sackton: No, I don't perform.
David S. Kong: No, you don't have to perform, you just have to do what you just did.
Mike: So… so Zeta, you'll… you'll fly up in your new costume that we're working on?
David S. Kong: There'll be some…
Mike: Some pieces that you can drop off it.
Mike: And Haskell catch him with his whip.
David S. Kong: I love this idea. So I'm sort of like, I'm disrobing for Heska.
Mike: It's a little bit like that.
David S. Kong: I'm dropping a little, but for Heska, for his benefit.
Mike: like, treats for him a little bit.
David S. Kong: I love this, and he's catching them, he's catching them.
Mike: Yes, yeah.
Mike: It could be. Yeah, but maybe a little bit, on the edge, right? Like, we don't want to take too much
Mike: Of the eyes away from you.
David S. Kong: You know what? Normally, I agree that all of the eyes should be on me, but in this particular case, I don't mind. This sounds great.
Mike: Yeah, but we want to give him a little,
Mike: a gentle introduction to your level of hormones, right? We don't want to overwhelm them.
David S. Kong: This all sounds fantastic. Hey, what's this name? Little… Little Joey? What's the, what's the,
Mike: Little Tony. It's important for me should you talk about this?
David S. Kong: I'm sorry, Sculpting, I'm sorry, I'm sorry. Little Tony.
David S. Kong: The things that are gonna be on my body that.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Hmm.
David S. Kong: And then, my man Heska here is grabbing.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Mmm.
David S. Kong: They need to be amazing.
David S. Kong: Do you… do you understand?
David S. Kong: We have, like, 3 hours now, because this whole situation is just taking time, which is fine, but you…
David S. Kong: Are gonna deliver.
David S. Kong: Right?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Mmm.
David S. Kong: Zeno, you come with me, I need to talk to you about some things, and everybody else
David S. Kong: let's work on this choreography, and little Tony, little Joey, whatever… little man, you go and get…
Mike: That helps outy.
David S. Kong: Little Tony, I'm so sorry. Little Tony, you go and find the things.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yes?
Mike: Like, remember what we talked about?
Mike: Not… not Pabbel… not Pebble person.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): - sparkly. Sparkly.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Jewelry. Yeah, no, no, I'm locked in, I'm locked in. Okay.
David S. Kong: It's a…
Eric Rosenbaum: So that's true.
Mike: You know, sometimes it's hard to remember the perspective shifts.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): It's that people just don't appreciate pebbles, like a pebble. Nope, I'm staying focused, I'm staying focused.
Mike: I had your stayed pretty… handballs are great. Look, you don't like.
David S. Kong: Little Joey, Little Joey, if you show up with a bunch of rocks after this whole call…
Mike: That'll be fun. That'll be fun.
David S. Kong: If little… if little man here shows up with a bunch of rocks.
David S. Kong: Sculpit, we are gonna have some big fucking problems.
David S. Kong: If this little man shows up with rocks.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): No, no, scope it. I gotta scope it. We gotta scope it.
David S. Kong: Is somebody gonna help him?
David S. Kong: Are you… are one of you two gonna help him? Make sure he doesn't go get a bunch of rocks?
David S. Kong: He's looking at anybody. It's like,
David S. Kong: Like, he's basically implying that little Tony, like, really needs a babysitter. Like…
Mike: That… that's probably true.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Which is probably, yeah, yeah.
Mike: M…
David S. Kong: I have an idea, I have an idea. Heska, you stay with me, because you should just be by me all the time. Sculpt it, you stay by me too, because the three of us gotta work on this a little bit. You two go and get the things. And she's looking at Zeno, like, my brother, like, you make sure that this… okay?
Eric Rosenbaum: I know a guy, and Zeno's like.
Mike: Nope.
Eric Rosenbaum: referring to the… Gem-studded scarf. My tailor. We'll go see him.
Mike: Sculpit will… Like, wave his head and create, like, a little image of, like, actual jewelry, like… Like this.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah, I got you.
Mike: Right?
Mike: Not… he raises his hand again, creates a little image of synthetic coolant pebbles.
Mike: Take these to the ball.
Mike: to the palm. Cool jewelry, but it's back again, back here.
Mike: Got it?
David S. Kong: Alright.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Did you catch that?
David S. Kong: So, we end this scene with,
David S. Kong: with, Heska and Sculptit and Xena staying behind to actually work on some of this choreography and just, you know, the flight patterns, when they're gonna go up, how it's gonna align with the music. Sculpit is in the zone now. Sculpit is, like, feeling the… he's like, okay, now that he's seen Heska do his thing, this whole thing with the whip and the things coming down, like, in Sculpit's mind, he's like, oh yeah, this is… this is gonna hit. Everybody's gonna love this.
David S. Kong: Very briefly, Little Tony and Zeno, 5-minute mini-quest. How are you getting objects? What's happening now? How does this… how is this working?
Eric Rosenbaum: I know a guy, Tony. When I need, like, a new, you know, piece of bling, I just go to my friend,
Eric Rosenbaum: Zare.
Eric Rosenbaum: And… and he's got my… he's got the goods. Let's go over there!
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Alright, alright. If he doesn't come through, I got a guy also. Let's start with your guy, though. Shut up, grass, I do stand up for myself.
Eric Rosenbaum: That's weird. Now, the… Zarit needs something in trade.
Eric Rosenbaum: Hmm, you got anything good?
Eric Rosenbaum: Not grass.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Check this shit out! And he pulls.
Eric Rosenbaum: I'll let you guys.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And opens it up, and it is pebbles. They're these little smooth Damn.
Eric Rosenbaum: We're gonna go see what happens.
Eric Rosenbaum: And so we fly over to, the… now, where's the tailor work out of? Just, like, under a tree.
Eric Rosenbaum: We'll do that.
David S. Kong: At this moment, with the festival, like, everybody's bringing little stations, and so.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, so he's got a…
David S. Kong: Yeah, there's a… you know where he is, you know where he is. And Zaer? Zaer, like, you know, he's known, he's known you for quite some time, but he's getting his whole tailor set up, and you know, again, it's a whole hustle and bustle, but he sees… he sees the two of you fly over, and he's like, Zeno, what's up?
Eric Rosenbaum: My man, I got an emergency last-minute request, submission critical for the Jubilee. Yeah, yeah, yeah, hit me.
David S. Kong: What do you…
Eric Rosenbaum: Beautiful bling. Just, A variety of small gemstones.
David S. Kong: Yeah, yeah, yeah, I got… and he, like, immediately, like, unfurls, it's like a rolled-up carpet, and it's like, boom, boom, boom, boom, like, red shiny things, like, sparkly purpley… this is, like, a whole giant array of things, and he's just like…
Eric Rosenbaum: Now, this is my friend Little Tony, he's gonna do the selecting. He's the, the connoisseur.
David S. Kong: Great.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Tony starts having a conversation with the jewelry that's out.
David S. Kong: But there's, like.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Alright, alright guys, listen up, listen up.
Eric Rosenbaum: Thanks for.
David S. Kong: Roll a, you have to roll something. Like, there's a whole thing about, like, how you do this well or not.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yes.
David S. Kong: What mechanic we came up with.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, I don't write that down in the notes.
David S. Kong: Let's just roll D20. Roll a D20. Roll a D20.
David S. Kong: Yeah, dude?
David S. Kong: And you can use your persuasion bonus, yeah.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh, shit, Natural20!
David S. Kong: What! Okay, so all of the gems, Schwartz, it's like…
David S. Kong: Normally, when you have objects that are talking to you, it is, like, so annoying because they're all talking to you at once, you can't pick out who's over who, you can't get any of them to shut up, like, you can't get this one to shut up versus that one to shut up.
David S. Kong: Right now.
David S. Kong: It feels like… there's probably, like, 30 to 40 individual gems on this, on this, like, rolled out, you know, rug thing.
David S. Kong: you feel like you've got perfect discrimination, and you can actually, like, hear every one of them. And it's like, it's blowing your mind a little bit, because this, like, super, super rarely happens that you have this clarity, but the gems, they're all there, and they're like.
David S. Kong: Pick me! Pick me!
David S. Kong: I'm cute!
David S. Kong: Bit mean?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah!
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, oh my gosh, I…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Here's what I need. I need gems to bedazzle a dazzling dragonette to be… to be, like, cast off over the crowd, like…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): you guys know what's up. Who works well together? I don't just need some nice gems, I need a team. Like, who.
David S. Kong: The Jets, like…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): team.
David S. Kong: the gems, like, they don't… it's not like they can, like, turn and look at each other, but energetically, that's what's happening. Like, they're all kind of, like, looking at each other.
David S. Kong: And there's, like, a one kind of platter that's got, like, a row of, like, you know, 25 of them, so, like, 3 or 4 per row, and they're all… you feel energetically all of them kind of, like, pointing towards this one, like, beautiful 8-sided ruby that's, like, sitting in the middle, right there.
David S. Kong: And, like, that one kind of starts pulsing a little bit, and the ones that are around it are, like.
David S. Kong: We think this is the one.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): look at you! You're so beautiful! And, like, all… all your friends just, like, boosting you up. This is what I like to see, like, the… the love that they have for you is what makes you so beautiful.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): This is magnificent, yes.
David S. Kong: The ruby is red and bright, and is blushing. The ruby is definitely, like… Oh, I've seen.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I feel the same, like, a moment like this. This is… this is Kuzmet, man, this is… ugh, this is beautiful.
David S. Kong: So Zaire is watching this whole scene, and he's sort of, like, kind of looking, looking at, you know, little Tony, like, he's like, are you…
David S. Kong: And he looks to Zeno, he's like, is he talking to the jewels? Is he talking to my jewels?
Eric Rosenbaum: It's his thing, it's… it's cool.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): No, man, I'm not talking to the jewels. The jewels are talking to me.
David S. Kong: Zaire's like, okay, I'm not sure exactly what's happening here, but it's a busy day, what do you have to trade?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): How do you like to do this? I have pebbles, cheese snacks, and a hermit crab shell.
David S. Kong: Show me the pebbles.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Alright, pull out the bag up now.
Eric Rosenbaum: Wait.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): These are…
David S. Kong: Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yep.
David S. Kong: You're Lil' Tony, right?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, man!
Eric Rosenbaum: This is THE little Tony.
David S. Kong: Wait!
Eric Rosenbaum: I heard of him, you know?
David S. Kong: Oh, wait, wait, wait!
David S. Kong: Do you have… A pebble butt?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh, shit, okay. I see you know your pebbles. It's not every day, I mean.
David S. Kong: I will buy.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): knows his pebbles.
Eric Rosenbaum: Hold up, hold up, huddle up, Tony.
David S. Kong: I heard a story about a pebble butt.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Dang, yeah!
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): The Pebble boat won third place at the Strange Things competition last year.
David S. Kong: I guess what I'm trying to say is, you still have the Pebble butt?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Okay, look, ordinarily, I use this bag of pebbles. This is my everyday bag of pebbles, but for you.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I'm gonna bust out the fancy pebble bag.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): He pulls out another sack, and opens this up, and fishes deeply in it, and pulls out a pebble.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Which, like, if we're being honest, it doesn't look that much like a butt, but it kinda looks like a butt.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Sort of understand why a person would say that.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And he, like, reverently lays it down.
David S. Kong: Zaire's looking at it, and is like, is this the one that won the third place in the competition last year?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, this is Edmund.
Eric Rosenbaum: Casino, like, gestures around like Edmund.
Eric Rosenbaum: Come on over to the side. You gotta get in the right frame of mind, you know what I'm talking about?
David S. Kong: They are tonic.
Eric Rosenbaum: Like.
David S. Kong: Schwartz Schwartz, is this the one that actually won the competition?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, this is the one, this is the one.
David S. Kong: Zaire gets out, like, you know, like a monocle, and is just, like, kind of looking closely at the butt, and is, like, rotating the butt, and is kind of just, like, staring, like, looking, looking, looking, and, like, looking at you, looking back at the thing, looking at Xena, looking back at the…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Alright, buddy, slow, slow, cool, cool it down, buddy, cool down a little bit.
David S. Kong: And then Zaire's like, Zaire's like, okay, okay, look, I don't have a lot of time, but…
David S. Kong: You get… 5 of whatever you want here, if I can get this pebble butt.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Listen, I will do this for you, but you have to promise me something. You have to treat Edmund right.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): You know? Edmund… Edmund's not garbage. Edmund's not just a rock.
David S. Kong: The pebble's name is Edmund?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That's correct. You gotta be decent to this dude. Like, you gotta respect Edmund, and Edmund will respect you. And if you can promise me that, we're done.
Eric Rosenbaum: We could also do a ton of temporary exchange. After the Jubilee, we just swapped them back, you know.
David S. Kong: No, no, no, no, no. That won't be necessary.
David S. Kong: Zaire, like, pauses.
David S. Kong: He has these, like, long, he has, you know, dragonett hair, but, like, you know, tied up into, like, a long… a long set of, braids in the back, and…
David S. Kong: Sort of looks down and is like…
David S. Kong: Edmund, like, speaking very, very, like, you know, down on one knee, looking at this pebble.
David S. Kong: Edmund?
David S. Kong: I promise to take care of you.
Eric Rosenbaum: That is the proper measure of respect there.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): You made me tear up, man. That's beautiful.
David S. Kong: You see, like, a lone tear, like, coming down Zaire's… like, a real one. Like, Zaire's, like, been thinking about this pebble butt, and the fact that it's about… he thinks he got a steal.
David S. Kong: For just trading, like, 5 random artifacts for the Pubble Blut, so…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): He may have. He may have. Like, little Tony's a little easy come, easy go on some things. Like, there's always more things to find, but he says, alright, Edmund, you've been like a brother to me all this time that we've traveled together. I'm gonna miss you.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Come see you sometime, alright? This is not the end of…
Eric Rosenbaum: 4 days.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): hanging out together.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): But you be good to him, he's gonna take really good care of you, man, alright? Alright, you take good care.
David S. Kong: Schwartz just… and just as a… just to close the scene, from the perspective of Edmund, can you get… can you give a little narration now of what Edmund is experiencing this month?
David S. Kong: Wrap this up.
Eric Rosenbaum: I love that.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Everything that's unfolded…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Like, with Edmund, the butt-shaped pebble, like, all of this is the briefest blink of an eye in, like, a life and epic journey that has gone on for thousands of years.
David S. Kong: God, like…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Ever since he was a portion of a statue crafted by the first inhabitants of the car ages ago.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And, like, the things that he's seen, how the world has changed, is just a blink, and like.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): So for Edmund.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): You know, this isn't the weighty, momentous occasion it is for little Tony, but… but there's something touching even to Edmund, after all these centuries, about the care that these two dragonettes are bringing, and Edmund feels good about this.
David S. Kong: And we close this scene with Edmund the Pebble butt, now reverently a part of Zaire's family of stones and pebbles and other collectibles.
David S. Kong: And so, little Tony, you work with, Zeno, and with your incredible communication and connection with, the various artifacts that are part of, Zaire's collection, find five immaculate pieces. And Zaire actually, in the end, is so grateful, he throws in a couple extra. So, you have…
David S. Kong: in a legitimate, objective way, at least as verified by Zeno and his taste.
David S. Kong: a fucking sick set of really cool jewelry. Like, kind of a belly, a belly, bracelet, like a piercing, like, you've got a really cool collection that you are now able to bring back over to, to Zeno and Heska and to Xena.
David S. Kong: And so, you do so…
David S. Kong: Zena is super, super ecstatic, and is happy, and prepares for… begins to get the preparations going, as now we're really, really getting down to it and getting close to the sunset. And so, as we shift into the start of the…
David S. Kong: great festival, and the Eightfold Festival, and to the Jubilee.
David S. Kong: It's been a very hectic day, and now, all of the Dragon Nets, as the setup is now complete and everything is about ready to go.
David S. Kong: the procession is starting to begin, and all across the island, all across these 8 communities of these Dragonette communities, they start to come and assemble, flying across the island and making their way to the Great Temple.
David S. Kong: And…
David S. Kong: as you all, settle down with your, communities, and I'm guessing, Little Tony and Sculpit, y'all are also part of the Wanderer community, I'm guessing, yeah? Even though this is a… you can… yeah. Does that work?
Mike: Yep.
David S. Kong: So, you all sit with your respective communities and, wait for the opening ceremony to begin.
David S. Kong: And the opening ceremony for the Dragonettes is indeed an important one.
David S. Kong: The open… the opening ceremony is…
David S. Kong: one of the very, very few times in Dragonette culture where there is actual solemnity
David S. Kong: And a big part of that is, number one, the appearance of the elders. So, each one of the eight gray Dragon Eck communities, they yearly will find one elder to come and represent, themselves, and represent their community as a part of the eight-fold ceremony.
David S. Kong: And…
David S. Kong: As all of the communities have settled down and everybody's, you know, taken their seats, there's some murmurs and hushes because the elders are starting to make their way, down from the back of the, the larger kind of stages, making their way towards the front.
David S. Kong: And each of the elders from each of the, the community's… Has a different representative.
David S. Kong: From the Dark Lady, there's a tiny, ancient, and impeccably dressed
David S. Kong: Dragonette with scraps of black, purple, and silver fabric.
David S. Kong: walking closely and, carrying a single black feather. And this is something you also always remember. Every one of the communities and every one of the elders is carrying some type of an artifact that's been blessed by their community and is going to be brought over to the center of the circle.
David S. Kong: From, from the mother, one of the elders,
David S. Kong: Carries with them a small piece of dried fruit that has been blessed by their community as a representation of food to be fed to the larger family of dragon nets.
David S. Kong: From Bright Faced, there's a ceremonial sash.
David S. Kong: And a polished disc, a mirror, that shines perfectly and brightly and tilted right towards the light and shines outwards and is brought over into the circle.
David S. Kong: And slowly, for each one of the communities, a different object is brought
David S. Kong: And brought forth into the center of the, the circle.
David S. Kong: And also, as this is happening.
David S. Kong: Another great moment for the community here are the clutches. All of the dragonette eggs that are currently still hatching, or in the process of going through this birth.
David S. Kong: Are, raised and are, lifted up and are visible, amongst the various tents, and these are in places that are really kind of sacredly, you know, designed and really set up in a very, very special, illuminated way, but…
David S. Kong: Also, again.
David S. Kong: For as wild and as funny and as sarcastic and whatever as the dragon nets are, the clutches in these eggs are so, so important to the larger community.
David S. Kong: And so the elders come, and they start their procession. Eight objects are arrayed around the circle.
David S. Kong: And each one of the elders, again, representing their local community.
David S. Kong: adorned with the culture of their… of their, larger Dragon Egg community, starts to make their way closer in towards the center of the… the eight-fold circle.
David S. Kong: And as they make their way towards the center,
David S. Kong: You can see these objects, the feather, the piece of fruit, the polished mirror, an iron ring, a colored glass.
David S. Kong: A stone?
David S. Kong: Little Tony, you recognize the stone. This is… and this one, it's interesting, because of your knowledge, is one of the oldest stones that you have felt on this island as being represented here.
David S. Kong: A living spring, a die.
David S. Kong: Much like Heska, you know how you were playing with the dice earlier, there's a, there's a die that's, brought in.
David S. Kong: And the eldest elder
David S. Kong: From Bright Face, steps forward with paint on their face, ceremonial in red and green and blue.
David S. Kong: And steps forward and has, a small staff with a gem on the top.
David S. Kong: And looks around at all of the 8 families and all of the 8 communities.
David S. Kong: And, you know, you feel, in this moment.
David S. Kong: A really special and deep connection to everyone here.
David S. Kong: You know, it's been such a crazy period, everybody preparing, but this moment right now is one where
David S. Kong: While there are 8 communities and all of the different clutches and the different siblings and the families, there's a real feeling of unity, a real feeling of connection amongst all of the Dragon Nets that are here.
David S. Kong: And, this elder, Walks into the center of the circle with the, with their staff.
David S. Kong: Arrays all of the objects, and, you know, solemnly points at each one.
David S. Kong: And then points over to each of the large statues that are surrounding the island.
David S. Kong: and says, 8 homes.
David S. Kong: 8 roads…
David S. Kong: And then, you know, kind of looks at everybody, because everybody knows what the call and response answer is going to be. And then everybody lets out this huge yell of one family.
David S. Kong: And there's a big, big, just kind of cheer, and everybody's, like, you know, hugging each other, and, like, just so fucking stoked to be there, and to be with everyone in this moment of, celebration and unity for this very, very special island.
David S. Kong: And as the words, one family, are said aloud, Sculpit. You know.
David S. Kong: That this is the time.
David S. Kong: And the moment that you all have been preparing for, Because now.
David S. Kong: The major, major kickoff set of performances is set to start.
David S. Kong: And you also know that Xena.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: This is her time to show me.
David S. Kong: And so, the four of you are…
David S. Kong: Very close to the front of the circle, you know, connected to your communities.
David S. Kong: But Sculpit, in particular, you know it's showtime.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And so…
David S. Kong: Xena is positioned where she's… needs to be, and she gives you a glance, and what do you do?
Tim Sackton: Can't you?
David S. Kong: Micro audio.
Mike: Can you hear me?
David S. Kong: I can hear you.
Tim Sackton: Now we can't hear you.
Mike: That might be together.
Mike: problems.
Mike: Like, is this just, like… Time to start the performance?
David S. Kong: Yeah. But Xena's, like, like, looking at you just, like, she's, like, you know, an extremely confident, you know, dragonette, but also.
Mike: I was like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like…
Mike: I'll, like, yeah, I've worked with her before, right? Like, I'll give her, like, a couple of, like, few words of encouragement, and, like, it's…
Mike: We've practiced this many times, like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like…
Mike: Let's go, let's… we've got this.
Mike: Back a shot.
David S. Kong: Are you gonna give her some advantage?
Mike: Yeah, yes, and Bardic inspiration.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Excellent.
David S. Kong: Excellence, excellence.
David S. Kong: And Huska, now that you all have done enough of this performance, where are you positioned?
David S. Kong: as this.
Tim Sackton: I'm next to Zeno, and I'm whispering to him, I didn't actually agree with this, did I? What was I thinking? What the hell is going on here? Get me out of this! Come on!
David S. Kong: Zeno, what do you do? What do you say?
Eric Rosenbaum: You got this, it's gonna be incredible. Your feats are gonna be so, tasty, they're gonna be edible! And, I'm gonna use my… my hype man…
Eric Rosenbaum: neck… Where if somebody else is trying to do something new, they add a D4.
David S. Kong: Hell yeah.
Mike: Aren't you a barg too?
Tim Sackton: Yeah, I'd also maybe give me some inspiration.
Eric Rosenbaum: And I also give you inspiration, exactly.
Eric Rosenbaum: Where's the mechanic for that? Oh, there it is, I'll check it off.
Eric Rosenbaum: So that gives you 1D6.
David S. Kong: Alright, y'all, so…
David S. Kong: as the one family moment happens, and everybody erupts into cheers, the Dragonette band starts to play, right? And every single one of the communities in the front, like, has a full-on
David S. Kong: set of instrumentalists, drummers, guitar players, and it's, like, a cacophony of sound, but also, like, sounds, like, surprisingly good. Because this is, like, the elite kind of set of musicians for each of the Dragonhead families.
David S. Kong: And so, the music starts.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And…
David S. Kong: In addition to Xena, there's a few other, you know, kind of side, like, in the front of each robe, there's, like, a set of, like, dancers, like, playing and spinning with fire, and then, you know, there's the music that's happening, but the aerial performance, this is where Xena, like, shoots up.
David S. Kong: And… so Zim's got advantage now?
David S. Kong: Is that right, Mike?
Mike: And the plus Webv6.
David S. Kong: What's that?
Mike: And the Barnic inspirations, like she gets asked for all these things.
David S. Kong: Alright, so, how do I roll for Zeno? Okay, first one. Roll?
David S. Kong: That's good. 17, and… let's do it again with advantage.
David S. Kong: Alright, and then I get a plus D6?
Mike: Yep.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): N plus a D4?
Tim Sackton: That's just for me.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh, that's weird.
David S. Kong: 23. Okay, so Xena launches up, and Xena now is adorned and bedazzled.
David S. Kong: She has got emerald earrings, belly ring, like, piercings on her nose, like, puts a claw in the air, like, launchers herself up straight in the air, and also trailing behind her. You don't know how or why this is happening, but there's, like, green smoke. There's, like, a rainbow smoke trail, like, almost like she's a jet with a wake, you know, like a rainbow wake behind her.
David S. Kong: She launches up in the air.
David S. Kong: And it's, like, doing just incredible swirls and twists.
David S. Kong: And then, you know, again, who knows exactly how this is happening, if there's an illusionist or whatever, but these artifacts start appearing, like, these different spinning, like, circles that she's, like, flying through, and she is diving, and Sculptit, you are, like, she is killing it. Because right now, all of the various kind of choreographies, and even, like, a couple of things that you didn't quite plan, you know, she was only supposed to do a single loop and ends up doing, like, a double-triple loop around it, but she's, like, feeling it.
David S. Kong: And you are… you are very, very happy at your people right now, that she's… she's really, really nailing it.
David S. Kong: And anyways, there's a couple of, like, associated other, you know, dancers and people that are flying, like, nearby, but, you know, they're all kind of doing, you know, supporting acts.
David S. Kong: And then she gets to the kind of key moment in this, like, opening performance, where now she's up at the top, and is about to shoot down, and she's gonna do, like, an up and down and shoot back up again, where the artifacts need to get pulled up and, like, need to be whipped.
David S. Kong: And now she gives you, Heska, like, the most loving look. Like, you are my man, and you are gonna deliver for me in this moment right now, when our entire community.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: be inside.
David S. Kong: The entire island. All eyes are on us.
David S. Kong: And Heska's gonna deliver.
Tim Sackton: Hasco nervously launches into the air.
Tim Sackton: And… goes for his…
Tim Sackton: Three ones.
David S. Kong: No!
Tim Sackton: possible role that Heska could get.
Tim Sackton: Launches into the air, is too nervous, trips, takes a whip, shoots it up towards…
Eric Rosenbaum: What?
Tim Sackton: up towards, you know…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Zena.
Tim Sackton: Hits her with the whip.
Tim Sackton: Turns bright red, and then suddenly this massive cloud of fog appears covering the arena, and nobody can see
Tim Sackton: Where, nobody can see anything. Like, 20 feet radius, fog cloud, passed a spell.
Tim Sackton: And… disappears.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh, Tony turns to skull, but that's…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That's not what you rehearsed, right?
Mike: guns? Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: We can work with this. We can… we can use this.
Eric Rosenbaum: We're gonna… we can bring it back.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Looks cool.
Tim Sackton: is…
Tim Sackton: Nowhere to be seen.
Tim Sackton: Oops, that was slate of hand. It's supposed to be stealth. Anyway, Hezka's hiding in this fog cloud.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh, we gotta… we gotta… we gotta, like, we gotta smuggle them out of here, right?
Eric Rosenbaum: Maybe we can recover from this.
Eric Rosenbaum: We can get the crowd into it.
Eric Rosenbaum: It's like a,
Eric Rosenbaum: You ever seen somebody, like, oh, it looks like they died on stage, but then, like.
Eric Rosenbaum: Actually, they weren't dead, they came back again. Wow! So what we have to have is Xena has gotta crash out.
Eric Rosenbaum: And then they're both gonna clear the fog and rise up! Whoops.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Skull, nobody… what do you think?
Mike: It looks like child needs.
Mike: I…
Eric Rosenbaum: I have the message cantrip that I could use to, like…
Mike: What?
David S. Kong: Okay, so this is all playing out in real time. Y'all are talking, trying to figure this out. The fog is starting to dissipate.
David S. Kong: And…
David S. Kong: Basically, like, it's a bit of chaos, because the band is loud, everybody's, like, kind of, like, dancing, but also, like, very much, like, loving watching Xena and all these acrobatics. And when Heska, like, hit her with the whip.
David S. Kong: Xena, because, like, Xena's, like, got heart eyes, like… like, looking down at Heska, the first, like, beautiful artifacts are, like, falling off of her, and it's just, like, the most… the scene is so perfect, you know? It's just… everybody's just, like.
David S. Kong: like, looking, and like, oh my god, this is the greatest thing we've ever seen. And, like, the jewels, as they're falling off each other, they're, like, following in these swirling patterns. And Heska, like, the initial kind of launch up is like, oh my god. Because, you know, people… Heska's low-key, but people do know about Heska, like, the crab story, all that, they know who he is. And everybody's a little like, oh, shit.
David S. Kong: Is this, like, combination, like, really happening?
David S. Kong: And when the whip goes up, and like…
David S. Kong: hits her in this just obviously, like, this is not correct kind of way. There's definitely an audible gasp, and there's a…
David S. Kong: Like, what was that? And it's sort of like, like.
David S. Kong: like, Heska, you get this sensation as, like, Xena's looking at you with all of the heart eyes, and the heart eyes, like, all instantly, like, evaporate. Like, they evaporate, and, like, the look in her eyes as she's looking at you… like, you know earlier when she was, like, talking to little Tony and was like, hey, you know, if you don't come back with the artifacts, I'mma kill you?
Eric Rosenbaum: Xena?
David S. Kong: is looking at you with just, like, the most, like, venomous death that you have ever, like, directly experienced, which is when you launch the fog, and all of a sudden.
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Like, no.
Tim Sackton: Nobody can see anything.
David S. Kong: Nobody didn't see anything, but you got, you, you got the daggers.
David S. Kong: As y'all are talking, the fog is, like, slowly starting to dissipate. Xena, who's also a pro.
David S. Kong: She's, like, takes advantage of the fog, like, somehow, and manages, like, to shoot out from the top of the fog, and, like, hovers over it, and…
David S. Kong: just, like, gives this big, like… even though, like, no… whether it was bad or not, she just acts like she won, like, the greatest competition in Sing-off.
David S. Kong: In the history of the Dragon X. And just, like, you know, shouts and is, like, puts out a victory sign, and her energy around that is, like, positive enough that, like, whatever they people saw, they just kind of remember her confidence at the moment, like, on top of this fog, just, like.
David S. Kong: I am the greatest. And the Dragon Nets, they still let out a big cheer. There's still, like, a lot of, like, you know, just, like, stoke. The stoke is still incredibly high.
David S. Kong: And, Heska, you are able to escape. You are able to, like, sneak out. And whether, you know, the lasting image of you, you know, like, unceremoniously, like, whipping Xena in a kind of, you know, obviously, like, failure way.
David S. Kong: lasts in everybody's minds for how long? We'll see, because everybody did kind of see that, but Xena, at least, with her own kind of sense of pride and her own sense of, like, I gotta rescue this.
David S. Kong: Is able to at least, you know, kind of restore some calm to the end of the performance.
David S. Kong: And so, all of the other performances, like, kind of wrap up, and what are the 3 or 4 of you doing as we're kind of engaging in this, like, post-performance thing? And because basically what's gonna happen is, as the performances die down.
David S. Kong: And as they get to the end, there is gonna be, like, one more kind of big moment, not involving, Xena or anybody else, but there will be one other big moment. That's the initiation of the games.
David S. Kong: And when the games start, that's when, you know, it's a bit of, like, you know, kind of… it's kind of like Burning Man, you know? There's, like, all of these different places you can go, wander off to, things you can go experience. So that part will happen, like, a little bit, but just in this, like, you know, kind of post-performance.
David S. Kong: Like, what are the four of you doing?
David S. Kong: Huska, where do you go, and where are the three of you?
Tim Sackton: So HESCA is… trying to… Like, sneak off through…
Tim Sackton: through the crowd, just, I mean, obviously.
Tim Sackton: It's, like, very bustling, and there's a ton of people around, but just,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You know, trying to…
Tim Sackton: Find some quiet corner where he can hide behind a wall or something like that, and eventually circle around to
Tim Sackton: Zeno, where he's gonna say.
Tim Sackton: This is why I don't do these things, never let me do that again. I don't know how that crazy person talked me into it.
Tim Sackton: But don't let me listen to anybody again. This is your fault!
Eric Rosenbaum: And Zeno's like, Yeah, we're gonna turn this into the most hilarious monologue.
Eric Rosenbaum: It's, we can work with this.
Eric Rosenbaum: Everybody saw it, but they don't even know what they saw. We're gonna tell the inside story, people are gonna love it.
Tim Sackton: Wowz the world, then.
Eric Rosenbaum: You ever hear the story of Cupid?
Eric Rosenbaum: We're gonna set the two of you up.
Eric Rosenbaum: Pierce.
Tim Sackton: hour with you.
Eric Rosenbaum: your era.
Tim Sackton: No, no, no, no, she wants to kill me now.
Eric Rosenbaum: Well, Well, we might have to work on that.
David S. Kong: To be fair, Zena's very hot and cold, and she often wants to kill everyone, so just, you know…
Tim Sackton: fire.
David S. Kong: Many road experiences.
Tim Sackton: NFR.
David S. Kong: No, you have not, you have not, and that was a particularly deathly stare that she gave me, so just…
Eric Rosenbaum: Two commercials.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oops.
Eric Rosenbaum: No, no, long time, Rev.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Little Tony's got into, like, a very quiet, like, whispered, but really heated argument with the bush right next to him, and you can hear him saying, like, listen, buddy, if you don't have something supportive to say, don't say it!
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Like, this is not the time to cr-set your fucking bush! Oh, that makes you mad? Yeah, come over here and tell me that. Oh, you can't? Because you're… fuck me? Fuck you.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): unsupportive. And, and, and turns back to, to Hesk and says.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): It ha- look, man, she didn't like you for YOU.
Tim Sackton: This is all of you. This is all of your fault. I wanted to just sit here and watch the games.
Tim Sackton: Oh, you enable him!
Tim Sackton: Little Tony.
Mike: You had some bad luck.
Mike: Right? That happens, we recover.
Mike: We move on.
Mike: Don't worry about it.
Mike: You were part of something great.
Eric Rosenbaum: What do we have…
Tim Sackton: Then we can do that.
Tim Sackton: That's called that.
Tim Sackton: Not listening to you again.
Tim Sackton: What does Sculpit… what does he wear? What does he, like, care… what does he look like? I didn't… I missed his description.
Mike: I never gave them. I believe about it, but he's like…
David S. Kong: Hey, Mike, your audio is still really weird. It's, like, not… it's, like, muffled and…
Mike: won't clear.
David S. Kong: like audio.
Mike: Is that any better?
Mike: I don't know, just plugged into my… Hold on…
Mike: I have a problem,
Mike: Is that better?
David S. Kong: Oh, there we go.
Mike: and was using my laptop mic instead of my fancy Jabra mic. Sorry.
Tim Sackton: The same one.
David S. Kong: And you got your… you got some fancy headphones on, but I'm not sure how it's working for you.
Mike: I was using the wrong mic. Okay, this should be much better.
David S. Kong: Excellent.
Mike: Sculpit is, like, fairly… I don't even have a good sense of what dragon ants wear, to be honest.
Mike: I… I vision… I envision him as kind of unassuming, and… and…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Wearing, sort of…
Mike: A fairly drab outfit, and… he doesn't carry that much stuff.
Tim Sackton: Okay.
Mike: he's more of… he's more up in his head than cares about physical stuff, right? Like, not pulling things out of his pockets or anything like that.
Mike: He probably carries almost nothing.
Mike: Look, it's an honor to perform however well we do.
Mike: You'll remember this forever.
Tim Sackton: Nesca just shakes his head.
David S. Kong: So, the four of you, as you're all chatting, and you know, Xena's, like, mobbed by fans, and it's just, you know… but also, again, like, at the end of the performance, right, it's like, there's this star-studded thing, but there's also, like, this… this… always, when the performances end, there's just very, like, you know…
David S. Kong: like, we are all one type of vibe. So, even with this, like, Zena, you know, after, you know, she kind of talks to people, like, comes over, and like, you know, finds…
David S. Kong: goes over and finds Heska, and, like, looks at Heska and is like.
David S. Kong: I'm never gonna forgive you for that.
David S. Kong: But good thing you're still cute.
Tim Sackton: Ask it turns bright red again.
David S. Kong: And, and Zena gives you, like, a quick little kiss on the cheek, and then, you know, bounces away.
David S. Kong: You are redeemed.
Eric Rosenbaum: Maybe I wasn't being ambitious enough. This could be the start of an incredible love story.
Eric Rosenbaum: We've got to play this up! Now it's your turn to play hard to get, my man.
Eric Rosenbaum: You gotta find another love interest for her to… Destroy.
Eric Rosenbaum: What's up?
David S. Kong: So as, as, you all kind of, you know, calm down from the end of the performance, and, the scene shifts now.
David S. Kong: into the post-opening ceremony, into now the Dragonet actual games. And this is very much kind of like a Burning Man sort of vibe, where there's, you know, a bunch of things happening in different spaces across the temple grounds.
David S. Kong: And, one place, though, Zeno, that you, in particular, are very excited about
David S. Kong: is the call and response, the spoken word showdown that happens every single year. And Zeno, for you, while Dragonettes are all family and all love.
David S. Kong: You do kind of have an arch rival.
David S. Kong: And your arch rival is Rosca.
David S. Kong: Who is…
Eric Rosenbaum: Nebraska.
David S. Kong: Oh, Rosca. Oh, Rosca. And Rosca is part of a larger crew of Dragonettes. You have your own crews as well, you know, everybody kind of floats around, but Rosca's crew is… the best way to describe Rosca's crew… let me,
David S. Kong: Let's go, let's bring, let's bring in Roscoe's crew.
David S. Kong: The best way to describe Rosca's crew is, like.
David S. Kong: It's like, if you… if you kind of imagine,
Eric Rosenbaum: -Oh.
David S. Kong: you know, this isn't the most representative image, but we'll roll with it. If you imagine signed a, kind of like Jamaican sound system culture.
David S. Kong: Where it's like, it's like, you know, the whole kind of idea is, who's got the best and coolest band?
David S. Kong: that can actually, like, you know, bring some, like, real, actual beats and music, and make the Dragon Ants dance the hardest. That is a big part of the energy.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And then, in the middle of the dance part.
David S. Kong: There's always the MC call and response.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: parts.
David S. Kong: That happens.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh, Scott.
David S. Kong: where MCs, the Dragon Nets, will get into the center.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: As they're dancing, but also having a call and response back and forth, and…
David S. Kong: Zeno, Rosca is one that you've been eyeing and kind of thinking about and preparing for, because you know that this was something that was likely to happen.
David S. Kong: And you see the four of you as you're kind of walking around and, you know, checking out various things. This is one of the first things that you come across, is Rosca and his crew.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Zeno, what do you do?
Eric Rosenbaum: So, I was kind of, like, occasionally mumbling all day, like, Rosa, I'm gonna toss, Rosca, you know, I gotcha,
Eric Rosenbaum: Rosa Rodatus. Wow. Guy, my eyes with… oh, man, I… this is what… this is why he's my rival. It's, like, very difficult to disparagingly run against him.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: But… I check out the setup.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Poke my claws into the speaker cones a little bit.
Eric Rosenbaum: What you got this year, man?
David S. Kong: Rosa, like, basically kind of looks and sees, like, the before of you, like, as a little mini crew, like, rolling up.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And Rosa looks over, Clearly noticing you and seeing you.
David S. Kong: And basically, Stops the music.
David S. Kong: Completely, and pauses, and is like, everybody stop.
David S. Kong: Everybody stop.
David S. Kong: I see you, Zeno.
David S. Kong: Where are you, Zeno?
Eric Rosenbaum: Bring it, my friend.
David S. Kong: Zeno, I've been waiting all year for this call and response battle with you.
David S. Kong: And now… You are going down.
David S. Kong: And he looks at the Hulker, and your whole crew is all going down. Are they all part of this, too?
Eric Rosenbaum: Is he not cast.
Tim Sackton: Slowly back away.
David S. Kong: Like, you know.
Tim Sackton: to the crowd.
David S. Kong: That's concluded.
Eric Rosenbaum: Boy, this is your chance!
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Little Tony's gonna put an arm around Heska, like, if you go, I'm going with you. I…
Mike: Sculpit will, like, go over to… to, you know, and be like, look.
Mike: we haven't really, like, like, practiced, I haven't really heard you to do anything, so… so I don't know how much advice I could… I could really give you, but look.
Mike: you're great, you're gonna be awesome, like, I really have faith.
Mike: That you will find a way to be your best self during the bits.
Mike: And you get a part of inspiration.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I'm just so brave.
Mike: And then he'll step away.
Eric Rosenbaum: Very simple, guys. Just follow my lead. You don't have to think.
Mike: I did my part.
Eric Rosenbaum: have to do is shout back.
Eric Rosenbaum: Whatever I say, okay?
David S. Kong: Dude, I just love this metagame, I just love how this particular group of Dragonettes, all of you are, like, fucking, like, shy, weird introverts, like, and none of you are, like, actually, like, part of, like, the core Dragonette culture.
Eric Rosenbaum: Good luck.
David S. Kong: Dancing and performing and all that shit, like, all of you are like,
David S. Kong: See, I'm gonna back away from all this whole situation. Let me awkwardly leave.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: roll.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Zeno,
David S. Kong: you know, Rosa… Rosa is… is, he's hyped to see you, but Rosca, you know, it's like… it's a dragon head thing, right? It's like, y'all are, like, enemies, but also friends, you know what I mean? Like, Rosa, like, you also will have, like, friendly battles with him, etc.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: But…
David S. Kong: this is, you know, this is the Jubilee, you know what I mean? This is the Jubilee. Everybody is here.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And, and…
David S. Kong: you know, Rosa wants a piece of you. You know, Rosa is ready for this moment.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So… Oh, Eric Roy, what'd you go? Oh, there you go. I just had to take something out of a toaster. I'm, like, making Lizzie's lunch while we're playing.
David S. Kong: You should do.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So basically, you know, part of what happens now is there's, like, a circle that's forming around you all. And, you know, Heska, Sculptit, Will Pony, y'all are in the circle.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Little Tony, you know, part of what's cool here is, like, this particular kind of Dragonet circle and this, this particular kind of call and response thing.
David S. Kong: This happens everywhere, but everybody brings some really fucking cool shit.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Indigenous.
David S. Kong: So it's, like, all across the island in particular, like, the Find It people, like, they're also adorning everybody that, like, you know, gets to come and dance in the middle. So there's just, like, you know, a bunch of, like, really cool objects for you to, like, both, you know, talk to and or be tortured by. But this is kind of another, like, another unique space for you.
David S. Kong: Heska, something that you, like, are really enjoying about this, because again, there's this whole dance battle part of it, and, you know, for you as, like, a hunter acrobat, like, it's really, really, like, hypnotic, like, watching the physical movements of some of these dragoneth, like, that's something that, you know, you're really appealed by.
David S. Kong: And Sculptit, you know, you're always, in these performance spaces, like, you can't turn off the part of you that's just, like, analyzing this shit and being like, ugh, you know, that was cool, but if you took that wing back and just did a little bit more of the shimmy.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I think the crowd would have liked.
David S. Kong: So all of you have, like, a little kind of, like, hook into this as…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Zeno…
David S. Kong: This is kind of your moment. And Rosa, like, kind of starts dancing in the middle.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And starts looking at you.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And he's like… Yeah.
David S. Kong: And he starts, like, wait, like, really? And, and, and Rosca's gonna, Rosa's gonna roll for his, his, his,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: His freestyles, hold on.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Go Zeno. Go Zeno.
David S. Kong: I'm, I'm gonna, I'm gonna go, I'm gonna go.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Something to him. I'm gonna go halftime.
David S. Kong: Hold on, hold on, I gotta find a guitar.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: a lot here.
David S. Kong: What's a good die roll for this? What should I… what would be a good,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like…
Eric Rosenbaum: Zeno's inner monologue here is like…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: He's feeling like…
David S. Kong: performance.
Mike: Yeah, performance, yeah.
Tim Sackton: performance.
Eric Rosenbaum: He's a little bit, like, under the odds.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like, he needs maybe a little special help.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: For what he's gonna do.
Eric Rosenbaum: Rock off, and I pull… I pulled.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: little, little magic…
Eric Rosenbaum: Like, I have the spell that can make him laugh uncontrollably.
David S. Kong: Oh, shit.
Eric Rosenbaum: Or, maybe I should use my, call and response Talents.
Eric Rosenbaum: On him, because normally you'd use it on your crew, and then the crab, like, doing your chant back and forth.
Tim Sackton: Wait, alright, also, you forgot…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You have… you should have 3…
Tim Sackton: 3 max.
Tim Sackton: Oops, that was the Kong.
Tim Sackton: I haven't… this is what I have in my notes.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, this is your third.
Tim Sackton: Everyone.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, yeah.
David S. Kong: That's a good one. I was missing that one. That is a good one.
David S. Kong: Dude, that's like your… that's like kind of one of your signature ones, dude. This is your moment.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah, that's the opening move, actually, yeah. I might escalate to spellcasting if I need to, but…
David S. Kong: Okay. Actually, let's roll initiative. Let's roll initiative.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, to see who just…
Tim Sackton: Who goes first?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: We were all, we were all initiative, hold on.
Eric Rosenbaum: That's a 16 for me.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Roscoe rolls a… 14, you win. You start.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yo, yo, let's go!
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh my god, I'm so unprepared for this!
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I'm gonna give you the biggest, heaviest, nastiest diss.
Eric Rosenbaum: You're gonna go under, so deep, so low.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Your toenails are gonna grow by the time they find you, because the rocks are gonna grind you. I'm burying you deep.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Down to the ground.
David S. Kong: Who's the.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Pump and pound, y'all.
Eric Rosenbaum: Alright, so should I… can I roll my sick breath?
David S. Kong: Yeah, roll your attack.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Or how does that work?
David S. Kong: We're… No, that's.
Tim Sackton: Stickburn's a minus 1d4 to Rosca's role. You should probably just roll performance for yourself.
David S. Kong: performance.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: to start out. Do it like a… like a whoever rolls higher wins.
David S. Kong: Yeah, yeah, roll D20 for performance.
Eric Rosenbaum: That'll be a 22.
Mike: That's your Bonic inspiration, too, right? Why not?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Well…
Tim Sackton: We might… might be muffle Rev.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: But also, you can remember, so use your sick burn.
Tim Sackton: to subtract 1D4 from his role.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Right.
David S. Kong: This is.
Mike: But I…
David S. Kong: This is like Street Fighter, there's a three-round affair.
Mike: Right, okay. So, maybe Bartic inspiration.
Tim Sackton: Hong, I sent you a.
Eric Rosenbaum: That was my inspiration, yes.
David S. Kong: Let me look at this message.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Also, keep some stamina in reserve to quickly punch a car.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Totally. To what? To let them… To what?
David S. Kong: Okay, so just… Raska is, like, decked out. Raska's got, like, you know, jewelry, he's got, you know, like, all, like, his costuming is, like, peak. And that's part of, like, his performance, like, he's got, you know, a proper… what's your performance plus?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Zena?
Eric Rosenbaum: 7 plus 7.
David S. Kong: Yeah, Rosca, Rosa, like, right now, he's got a plus 8. Like, he's, like, he's, like, looking fire.
Eric Rosenbaum: Damn.
David S. Kong: Definitely, like, it's all decked out, jewelry, costuming.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Braids, like, everything, like feathers, he's just, he's totally decked out.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So Rosca's like…
David S. Kong: Okay, so you, you did your, you did your, what was your, what was your role again?
Eric Rosenbaum: anytime.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 22, okay.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So Rakut's like, zeno, gonna burn you to the ground!
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You're lost and found!
David S. Kong: You're like a little mound!
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Of dirt!
Audio shared by David S. Kong: That I walk on!
David S. Kong: And I jump on! And I piss on! Because you're dirt!
David S. Kong: And I'm Rosca!
David S. Kong: And I'm the best!
David S. Kong: And Rosca, Rosa, you know, he's… he's definitely, he's definitely, like, throwing the fire. Like, you're feeling a little, like, oh, shit, Rosca's definitely bringing the heat today.
David S. Kong: And he rolls… Let's see, do I have to do a minus D… a minus… Minus 4, yeah.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, let Eric roll the D4.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, nice, okay. Oh, dude, okay.
David S. Kong: Rosca rolls a 19.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: All in.
David S. Kong: minus…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And then D4… is a 3.
David S. Kong: So basically, this first round, you know, after, like, this back and forth that's happening, and all the Dragonettes, they're kind of bouncing and looking, and you know, they're cheering as, like, kind of each moment happens, but then it's like, you know, kind of once Raska finishes, you know, there's the MC Dragonette that kind of stands up in the middle, and then basically, like, points first at, like, Rosa, and everybody cheers, but then he points over to you, to Zeno, and then everybody's like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like, big, big, big roar. And Zeno takes round 1.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Of the Rosca face-off.
David S. Kong: Let's roll initiative around.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: That's true.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Switch, switch, I like this. Okay. Oh, that's a 10.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 15, Rosa gets the first round.
David S. Kong: Rosca now is, like, he's pissed. He's like… Rosa does not like to lose, and the fact that he lost that first round, he started to, like, feel a little something-something, so… He, like, reaches into his… oh, hold on.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah, so…
David S. Kong: Rosa, like, he's like… like, and you know Rosa, too. Like, Rosa typically in these battles, like, he gets more and more elaborate with, like, props and stunts. It's sort of like the NBA dunk contest, you know, it gets more ridiculous.
Eric Rosenbaum: Nice.
David S. Kong: round as it goes. The first round was just, like, verbal battle, but now this round, he's, like, starting to reach for his props. Like, he's got, like, you know, he's starting, like, as he's, like, rapping, and as he's doing his thing, he's, like, pulling out, like, feathers from his hair, and he's like, like, you know, yeah, like, you're terrible, like, the weather, and I beat you with this feather, you know, and he's like, you know, like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Pulling.
David S. Kong: about objects and, like, making rhymes, like, clever rhymes, like, with the different things.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And so, Tim, what happened?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Are you gonna do it?
Tim Sackton: Yeah, but I failed.
Tim Sackton: Number one!
David S. Kong: Set, chat, what's that?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, too.
David S. Kong: You see Rosa, and he's like, he's like, you know, because, like, one of the big things at Jubilee is, like, people playing with eggs, you know, because this is, like, the big… and oh, I should have mentioned earlier, it's like, if a dragon that actually hatches at the Jubilee, it's, like, fucking mayhem. It's like, oh, fuck, like, an actual, like, hatchling, like, occurred at the Jubilee.
David S. Kong: So there… but people have a lot of fake eggs, and there's also, like, games around, like, stealing eggs. Like, the actual eggs are in these, like, revered locations where nobody ever touches, super solemn, nobody would ever fuck with the eggs. But, like, the actual, like,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like.
David S. Kong: play eggs, they're, like, everywhere. It's like, Rosa's, like, reaching in his pouch, and he's ready for, like, super good burn, like, around, like, he's gonna be like, oh, yeah, and, like, I'm gonna hit you with my neck, just like you were my clutch thing in my egg! And he's about to, like, say egg, and he's, like, pulling… reaching into his pouch to pull out an egg, and he's sort of like, wait, is something… and then… but then he, like, finds it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And I pulls it out.
Mike: No balloon.
David S. Kong: Rivers!
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The spike!
David S. Kong: Despite the best intentions of Peska and his efforts to try to disrupt Rosca's flow.
David S. Kong: And he delivers… he delivers still a sick burn. And, let's see, he rolls as a part of his round of performance.
David S. Kong: A 20, in total.
David S. Kong: 12 plus 8.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Alright.
David S. Kong: Alright, back to you.
Eric Rosenbaum: I'm getting ANTA.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah?
Mike: Nothing. I'm not doing anything.
David S. Kong: Do you have, you do have an advantage or anything? It's just regular, regular D20 on this phone?
Eric Rosenbaum: I guess so.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Alright. Nice.
Mike: We never really mechanically decided how my advantage thing works, but my sense of it is I have to see you in private first, and, like, give you.
David S. Kong: Yeah, yeah, yeah. Did you get an advantage on the first one?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: No. No.
Tim Sackton: No, it was a straight roll.
Eric Rosenbaum: I have my inspiration still, so I can use that, this rune, if I need to.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Alright.
David S. Kong: You won the first round, though, so that's good.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Roscoe, you got nothing.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I got my crew.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: We're gonna roll right over you.
David S. Kong: Whoa!
Eric Rosenbaum: Coming out of nowhere gonna get ya. Here comes my boy, Heska.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh, no.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Here comes my little Tony.
Eric Rosenbaum: He's gonna look at you and see you're a phony.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, God.
David S. Kong: I'm gonna have to, like, kind of lose… Melanie.
Eric Rosenbaum: Crew, we're better than you. And now I'm up on my pulpit like a prophet.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: With my boy, Sculpit. We're gonna knock it right down!
Eric Rosenbaum: Don't mess with my crew.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: will crush you.
David S. Kong: Okay, okay, on the strength, on the strength of, like, just the performance… You should get it. Yeah, you get an additional, you get an additional plus 5 on that.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So, like…
David S. Kong: Add a plus 5 to whatever your performance roll is. That was sick.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay, let's roll it. That's a 25 out of the gate, so a 30 total.
David S. Kong: Wow! After, after, after you call Rosa a phone.
Tim Sackton: Like, almost a seeker role.
David S. Kong: After, after you call Rosca a phony.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: like, everybody, like, erupts, and, like, Rosa… Rosa just, like, looks at you, and he's like… he gets down on a knee, and he's like…
David S. Kong: He's just like, game recognizes game, that's it. He's like, I'm done.
David S. Kong: And then, like, Roscoe, like, comes over and gives you, like, a big hug, and he's like, dude, you killed that. That was crazy. That was crazy. And everybody is just like…
David S. Kong: And, and, you know, you get mobbed. Like, everybody, like, the whole big circle kind of, like, bounces, bounces, bounces, and, like, everybody's, like, kind of bouncing around you, and, like, Heska and little Tony, and you all just get kind of, like, you know, like, none of the three of you, like, fucking awkward-ass nerds, are like, oh, no, we're getting pulled in the middle of, like, the bouncing thing. But you can't, like, you're, because of your progress, you just get, like, pulled in, and you're, you're all kind of around, around,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Around, Xeno.
David S. Kong: And all of you are just, like, kind of experiencing this, like, mob of, like, Dragonet, like, hype energy and stoke around… around your… the sickness of your burn.
David S. Kong: Amazing.
David S. Kong: So… Basically, after, after this, this, the, this battle, which was, an epic, epic battle,
David S. Kong: And we're getting to, like, 11, right? How late are we going here?
Tim Sackton: We can go, I mean… We can stop. If you run out of step, you've prepared.
David S. Kong: Oh, no, there's more, there's more, no, no, I'm…
Tim Sackton: We can go… it's only 11 now, we can go for, like, 30…
Tim Sackton: I mean, we sometimes play as late as midnight, but let's keep going, for sure.
David S. Kong: Okay, let's, let's, let's do… we're gonna do one more, one more.
Eric Rosenbaum: I don't know if I have another rap battle in me, but I want to play more.
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Dude, you killed that, Eric? That was, like, like, legit. You, like, you destroyed me, man. That was, like, rock the guy worked.
David S. Kong: That was.
Eric Rosenbaum: That was…
David S. Kong: Insane. You nailed that.
Eric Rosenbaum: There was enough time for me to mentally prepare, so… Yeah.
David S. Kong: did ultimate sick burns.
Eric Rosenbaum: That was awesome.
David S. Kong: Alright, so as, as we shift into, to nighttime, and hold on, let me just…
Eric Rosenbaum: I don't think I could beat Kong at his full power, though.
David S. Kong: Adjust, adjust… no, that was, that was… you totally beat me up at full powers.
David S. Kong: As we shift into, Shift into nighttime.
David S. Kong: you know, there's a… there's, like, the… it's, it's a, you know, I mean, this is the… the night, you know? So, there's ebbs and flows throughout the whole evening, but…
David S. Kong: You know, the four of you take some time, after, you know, like, enjoying the revelry of,
David S. Kong: hold on.
David S. Kong: of enjoying the revelry of, of, Zeno's victory over Raska, and, you take a little time, and you're all… you're all hanging out. Actually, where are you hanging out? You guys, there's a whole bunch of different places. I'm not gonna… we're not gonna do, do the actual,
David S. Kong: scenes just to save a little bit of time, but, let me just give you a couple of options for places that you could be. So…
David S. Kong: There's The Great Find, which is where, you know, people just bring, like, all kinds of crazy fucking awesome objects and, like, share them with each other to look at. There's The Great Feast, where, like, people bring, like, really fucking crazy awesome food to, like, show off and also eat.
David S. Kong: There is… we saw the call and response,
David S. Kong: There's also, there's a bunch of, like, acrobatics places, you know, there's different folks, there's, like, water acrobatics, like, on the edge of the island, so I would say, like, those are the main three different kind of places you could go. There's acrobatics, food, and or find. Like, those are different areas. So which one… which one are you at? You, you know, you could have, you could have explored various places throughout the earlier part, but where do you, where do you end up as you, as we get towards, you know, kind of into the evening?
Mike: I mean, I think Scalpin would always be drawn towards Acrobat, to a more performant performance, but could go anywhere.
Mike: I would be at the acrobatics by default, unless…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Let's get food, like, the night is wearing on, I feel like this is the… this is time to go get some food.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah, to stop going.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Going to performances.
Tim Sackton: Haske is, he's pretty done with the Jubilee at this point.
Eric Rosenbaum: It's been a rough day for Eska.
Tim Sackton: He's… So he's,
Tim Sackton: He's… he's, you know, on the sort of edges of… of the festival a little bit,
David S. Kong: How about this? How about this? You guys go to, the, to go get food, and each of you, you spend some time there, finding, like, some interesting things, you know, obviously hanging out with other dragon ants, but then you go…
Eric Rosenbaum: This fish cake looks like a butt. Yeah.
David S. Kong: And in a moment, describe what you get, because it's sort of like, you know, it's like street fair style, but, like, you also, like, you know, spend time, like, you know, reveling in, like, the awesomeness of the thing with whoever caught the thing. So, you know, pick a cool thing that you're gonna eat for dinner.
David S. Kong: And then you guys all then, like, head up, you know, to kind of a part of the temple grounds where you can sit up above.
David S. Kong: And kind of look down at everything. So this is the view, basically. You're kind of looking up at above, like, down at the whole temple grounds, but you finally have a little bit of space, you know, a little bit of… away from the cacophony to have a little moment for just the four of you to hang.
David S. Kong: So, so what are, what are each of you, eating in this, in this moment?
Eric Rosenbaum: Zeno has got, like, a mouthful of, like, a fish meatball, but he's, like, so excited he can't control himself, reenacting, he's like, yo, yo! And then I was like, whip! I was like, what kind of rhyme with this guy? It's like, yeah, Chad, I was like…
Eric Rosenbaum: He's just, like, obsessively reenacting.
Tim Sackton: So, so Haske has left the festival a little bit early than everybody else, and the Jubilee, and flown up here,
Tim Sackton: Just on the way, like, dipping through… dipping down into the forest where, you know, where he…
Tim Sackton: Flies around a little, and there's, you know, there's these rivers that run down from the top of the mountain.
Tim Sackton: Dips down and catches a few trout. Something simple, something that he reliably knows that he can always catch.
Tim Sackton: and flies back up, and as everybody kind of drifts up to this overlook after getting food, or watching the acrobatics, or what everybody else is doing, Heska's got, like, two trout.
Tim Sackton: Grilling over a fire, and it's just, like, you know, picking… picking through them, eating the fish, like, you know.
Tim Sackton: Claws and teeth, you know, ripping the flesh out and…
Tim Sackton: Sitting, kind of, maybe with his back to the festival until… Everybody starts to show up.
David S. Kong: Heska, what's your… what's your emotional state right now, after…
David S. Kong: I mean, just candidly, the most embarrassing moment of your entire life, but…
Eric Rosenbaum: Did you roll any dice that we're.
David S. Kong: Not to rub, you know.
Tim Sackton: I rolled… I rolled 5 dice, and they were all 1s.
David S. Kong: I mean, this is… I'm not even positive.
Mike: Statistically, just…
David S. Kong: Heska, how are you doing? How are you doing in there?
Tim Sackton: So… So, Haske, I mean, this has just solidified his…
Tim Sackton: determination that he is never going to attempt to perform, like, it's a fool's quest. Like, no, performance…
Tim Sackton: It's not for him.
Tim Sackton: He's gonna just sit behind the bar of the… Dark buckle, or whatever.
Tim Sackton: Zeno ends up calling it.
Tim Sackton: He… Heska's calling it the dark buckle nut.
Eric Rosenbaum: That's gonna help.
Tim Sackton: nails.
Eric Rosenbaum: A dark buckle.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Bilton.
David S. Kong: Honey, what are you, what are you eating?
David S. Kong: dinner situation.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Little Tony is super sick, because he's eating lobsters, and the thing is, Little Tony never catches and eats lobsters, because lobsters all talk to each other. And if you eat one lobster, like, every other lobster is, like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Fuck that.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That guy, he eats us. So, like, this is the opportunity to, like, get away with eating lobsters. It's especially bad, too, because his favorite part is the face, and so he is just, like, chomping on lobster faces. And, like, some part of him feels bad about it, because, like, he knows a lot of lobsters, but also…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I don't know, he's a little philosophical.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): So he's got, he's got, like, a skewer that is as long as he is, with just, like, a row of lobsters that have all been roasted over a big flame. He's just chomping their faces off.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: M…
Mike: Skull Butt has somehow ended up with, like, a…
Mike: He doesn't usually, like, work with people in the… like, he's not usually… he's not really a foodie in any sense, but, like…
Mike: he, like, knows somebody who, like, worked with, like, and so he ends up, like, talking for a while to one of the, like.
Mike: Fancy Hunters who has made this, like, weird seafood delicacy.
David S. Kong: Yo.
Mike: like, mixed, like… like, intermixed crab and shellfish and fish, kind of, like a turducken kind of style, but with, like, but with, like, fish and crab and oysters or something like that.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And he's sort of asked.
Mike: absent-mindedly, like, taken some, because he was chatting with the guy, because they had, like, worked with the same person a while ago. And… and then, like, wanders up to these guys, like, not paying that much attention. They're like, oh, wait, no, I… I apparently have a very elaborately created,
Mike: fish…
Mike: fish ab oyster, I don't know, right? Like, and he kind of comes out, he's like… he's, like, kicking himself that he didn't spend more time with Heska, because, like, if only he had, like, given Heska advantage instead of…
David S. Kong: Sculpt it, sculpt it, you're… as… whatever, like, Heska's experiencing, sculpt it, you definitely feel like a burden, like, oh, fuck, like, you know, like, you know, as a coach on this situation.
Mike: Well, he's proud of how Xena recovered, and like, he still feels like her performance went really well, but he's like, I really should have spent time with this guy, right? Like, he… I dragged him into it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Right?
Mike: I convinced him to do this, and then I kind of abandoned him from my primary client after, like.
Mike: putting the minimal effort into him, and he feels really bad. He's like, do you like this food? Like, do you want some of my crab duck in here? Like, would you like getting… I feel bad, right? Like, he's, like, trying to make it up to Heska, like, this was probably… it probably should have helped you more, right? Because, like, I see you were so close, like.
Mike: Like, like, actually, you were almost brilliant. You were, like, steps away from being brilliant.
Mike: He was! No, no, seriously, like, like… The rehearsal was great!
David S. Kong: The rehearsal was amazing!
Mike: Listen, listen, it's a little, like, his movement was right, like, sometimes the biggest mistakes are when you're the closest to success.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Hmm.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, true.
David S. Kong: He's go.
Mike: Right?
David S. Kong: Asko, does that hit you? Are you… or is that…
Tim Sackton: No, no, no, no, no.
Mike: I don't know.
Tim Sackton: Barking up the wrong tree, fella!
David S. Kong: Zeno, what's your dinner?
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, I was just working on, octofish crab puss concept.
Eric Rosenbaum: Well, it's like, what's the seafood turducken?
Eric Rosenbaum: And it turns out I am better at that than Claude.
Eric Rosenbaum: And I would give me cooking tips, actually, like, when are you thinking of repairing this?
Eric Rosenbaum: There's a timing issue. Zeno is eating…
Eric Rosenbaum: Just your basic working man's fish meatballs on a stick, but he can put away a ton of them.
David S. Kong: And as you're all, kind of sitting up and eating and…
David S. Kong: You know. Is there, is there anything, any other conversation you want to have with each other? Any, any other, any other, either shout-outs to Rosca or, you know, love to Heska from, from the day? Anybody wants to share?
Eric Rosenbaum: Can't wait.
Eric Rosenbaum: To, see what Raska comes back with next year.
Eric Rosenbaum: Man, he's gonna be motivated.
Tim Sackton: Maybe we'll finally have your club ready. You can practice, you know?
Eric Rosenbaum: Well, you guys are my crew now, you're already legendary! You were in the… you were in the battle, so… you know, we're gonna have to have, like, matching outfits and shit next year.
Mike: Look out. You did well. Like, I could see a few places you could do a little bit, but we could talk, let's talk later, right? Like, I think I could really help you if you want.
Eric Rosenbaum: I would love some tips.
Eric Rosenbaum: You know, like, making things scan…
Eric Rosenbaum: Getting the… getting the appropriate diction for the audience, and so forth.
Mike: Yeah?
Mike: Very important, right? Know your audience. I said, you're… you have the makings, right? You're on the right track.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Really, really liked.
Eric Rosenbaum: Next, Rev.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I really liked the part where you were rhyming. Like, that was… that was my favorite part.
Eric Rosenbaum: You were in it too, though, my man.
Mike: That was all the parts, though.
Eric Rosenbaum: Most of them, anyway.
Mike: I…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Little Tony looks up at the sky.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): at a cloud overhead and says, like, listen, buddy, this is not the time. Like, this is a beautiful moment of common peace. Just, like, keep going. He's, like, trying to wave this cloud onwards.
David S. Kong: Schwartz, as you're in the middle…
David S. Kong: Of having this conversation with the cloud.
David S. Kong: And, you know, again, all day, you are just constantly in this situation of just, you know, having to deal with more conversation, more of this, like, more of that.
David S. Kong: Something happens that, for you.
David S. Kong: Maybe has never happened to you before, that you've ever experienced.
David S. Kong: And as you're talking to the cloud, Suddenly, the cloud… Goes completely silent.
David S. Kong: And not only does the cloud go completely silent, But as you sit there, You realize that
David S. Kong: There's no sounds at all.
David S. Kong: From anything.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): A little Tony…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Drops the lobsters on the ground and stands up and says to the three of you, without, like, looking, just like, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Do you guys hear that?
Mike: Has anything changed?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Is anything different in the world, like, for the three of them?
David S. Kong: S. Right.
David S. Kong: You are noticing that there is no sound? Like, at all. Like, just zero, zero sound?
David S. Kong: Zeno, you noticed in your mind's eye, or your mind's ear, as it were.
David S. Kong: like a tone. Like, there's a sound that's in your mind. But, like, a beautiful note. It's… maybe the most beautiful note you've ever heard in your entire fucking life.
David S. Kong: And, you know, you're a spoken word guy, but you're a musician, you know? And so, there's something about this note that feels so sacred, and so full of awe, and so full of beauty, and…
David S. Kong: It's suddenly in your mind.
Eric Rosenbaum: You guys hear that? That's amazing.
Tim Sackton: You're what?
Eric Rosenbaum: It's, it's indescribable. Zeno looks down at his fish meatballs, say, like… I think these are fresh.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And, like, cut…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Guys, he says to the bush you're next to, and, like, hits the trunk of the tree a few times, like.
David S. Kong: Nothing.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Guys?
David S. Kong: Nothing. No response.
David S. Kong: Sculpt it as you are… Sitting and kind of looking at your comrades and wondering what's happening.
David S. Kong: One thing that you have not mentioned at all is your relationship with magic.
David S. Kong: Sculpt it, roll a D4.
David S. Kong: you are now feeling something that you know happens every once in a while, and Lil Tony, you maybe have seen this happen as well before.
David S. Kong: Do you know what this is?
Mike: Yeah?
David S. Kong: What are your role?
Mike: Trade.
David S. Kong: Sculpit disappears.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Whoa.
Tim Sackton: What's up with your friend?
Eric Rosenbaum: Where'd he go?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Buddy, stay really still.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Sculptit,
David S. Kong: You reappear, like, about 20 feet away from the group.
David S. Kong: And…
David S. Kong: Yeah, you appear, like, 20 feet away from the group, like, in a spot just behind them, like, up.
David S. Kong: Up, and, like, if you were to kind of look at the all… all of the eight statues, like.
David S. Kong: you're in, like, a direct line to, like, the Wanderer right now, but boom, 20 feet back.
Mike: I walk over that direction, is anything happening over there? Does anything look unusual?
David S. Kong: At the Wonder.
Mike: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Nothing at the moment.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Sort of, like, looking down and out across the festival, like.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Does everything still seem normal down there? There's not, like, a wave of discontent.
David S. Kong: The world seems totally normal. Seems totally normal.
David S. Kong: And Heska, Heska, roll, do a perception check… perception check?
Tim Sackton: 14.
Mike: Wasn't a one?
Tim Sackton: 101.
Eric Rosenbaum: Hi, Courtney.
David S. Kong: Do you have a… is that with a bonus? Like, you're…
Tim Sackton: Yeah, plus 3. Okay. So that's the total.
David S. Kong: Aska, you notice, again, with your hunter's eye,
David S. Kong: As all of this has been unfolding, unspeakably, there was some kind of object. It looked like something…
David S. Kong: Was in the sky, moving. Like, kind of…
David S. Kong: just darted off. Like, you couldn't exactly catch what direction, but there was definitely, like, a weird shadow and an unnatural movement up in the sky that you noticed.
Tim Sackton: I'm gonna… Buy up… try and chase it. I'll tell every… I'll say to… to…
Tim Sackton: Zeno, and to the crew. Something's flying up there.
Tim Sackton: that I'm gonna fly after it.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, I immediately hop up in bolts.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): As quick as I can. Like, I am profoundly spooked by what is going on.
David S. Kong: Yeah, I'll…
Mike: And it doesn't seem to be flying towards the Wadra statue.
David S. Kong: What's that?
Mike: deploying towards the wanderer?
Tim Sackton: I only kept… limbs.
David S. Kong: Yeah, you caught a glimpse, but.
Mike: How far away?
David S. Kong: It could have been in that direction. It was… it's far off in the sky, like.
Mike: Okay.
David S. Kong: Distant, distant.
David S. Kong: Schwartz… Schwartz, you said that, Little Tony takes off and flies as well?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
David S. Kong: When you get off the ground and start flying up.
David S. Kong: It's really fucking weird, but, like, the silence is louder.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, yeah, yeah.
David S. Kong: You know, what are you doing? Really fast.
Eric Rosenbaum: I'm following, I'm flying.
David S. Kong: Xeno…
Eric Rosenbaum: I was going into novelty, trying something new.
Tim Sackton: I'm trying to get high up so I can, like, try and see if there's anything else in the sky, or like…
Tim Sackton: See this… spot this thing again, or just, like, try and get a sense of… What's going on?
David S. Kong: Zeno, as you, as you take off into the sky, and you actually roll a perception check.
Eric Rosenbaum: That's a 22, natural 20, with a plus 2.
David S. Kong: Oh, okay. Hell fucking yeah.
David S. Kong: Okay, as you…
David S. Kong: Take off. And again, all of you are kind of, like, moving in a similar direction, or at least taking off now into the air.
David S. Kong: you notice something really fucking interesting. Like, as you take off into the air.
David S. Kong: This note is still in your head, like, you can still feel this note in your head, but as you,
David S. Kong: As this note is resonating.
David S. Kong: What you're noticing is that the volume of the note seems to be changing depending on the direction that you're flying.
Eric Rosenbaum: I don't know.
Eric Rosenbaum: Where I'm going is.
David S. Kong: Certain directions it's getting louder, and then certain directions it's getting solid. Like, you definitely notice that there is, like, a trend, for sure.
Eric Rosenbaum: So I'm… I'm swerving around, trying to, like, home in on it.
David S. Kong: Okay. So, as you're kinda… so, okay, so you're swerving around trying to home in. Little Tony, what are you doing?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): This silence thing for me, it's not just like the world is quiet, it's like it's being muffled by something, like something has come over the sound of the world.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yes.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I'm… I'm gonna try and, like, intensify. I'm just gonna, like, keep going up.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Like, I'm trying to understand what this thing is, like, if there's a quality of, like, a gradient to it, to try and follow that.
David S. Kong: Yeah, similar… actually, do a perception check?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): 22 altogether.
David S. Kong: Alright.
David S. Kong: You similarly notice that as you're flying around, this weird-ass phenomenon of
David S. Kong: the, silence getting louder also has a directionality. There's, like, something about it that feels to shift depending on the direction you're in.
Eric Rosenbaum: care.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, I'm gonna try to hum along with it, too.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Eric Rosenbaum: Just… just see what happens. I'll match the note with my voice.
David S. Kong: Okay, okay, very cool.
David S. Kong: Yeah, when you hum with it, It feels good.
David S. Kong: There's something about it that feels like… like…
David S. Kong: It's hard for you to describe, but, like… because this is kind of a freaky moment, you're all a bit, like, kind of in a panic around, like, what the hell's happening here, there's a lot of… but… but… For sure, like, harmonizing with it, like, there's something about that that feels…
David S. Kong: Your system feels really good about this.
David S. Kong: There's, like, some kind of piece that… it's… but it's fleeting. It's fleeting, but it's definitely there when you hum with it.
David S. Kong: What else, what else are you doing now?
Tim Sackton: So, right now, Little Tony and Zeno are, like, flying ar- Around in circles.
David S. Kong: They're flying erratically. If you guys haven't been talking to each other, they're just like… they're flying erratically, and then…
David S. Kong: And then, and then, yeah, so then, so what are… what are you…
Tim Sackton: I'm still… I'm still flying up, watching, and I'm trying, like…
Tim Sackton: I'm pretty sure something's going on with them, I'm just trying to see if there's a pattern, like, are they…
Tim Sackton: Are they moving in similar ways? Are they, like…
Tim Sackton: like, can I infer anything about their behavior from observing them from above?
David S. Kong: Make another perception check.
Tim Sackton: And I argue this should be investigation, not perception.
David S. Kong: Yes, go for it.
Tim Sackton: 14.
Tim Sackton: My highest roll of the night.
David S. Kong: Okay, I mean, you know, I'll give you that. So, so 14.
Tim Sackton: Except the one time I rolled with Advantage.
David S. Kong: Oh, Heska. So, with a 14, you notice, like, with all of the weird, like, kind of back and forth that the two of them are having, there does seem to be a bit of a pattern. Like, they kind of, like, you'll see them kind of both, like.
David S. Kong: going in the same direction a bit, and then, you know, kind of shifting, and then going in the same direction a bit, so there does seem to be some convergence around, like, what it is that they're…
David S. Kong: How it is that they're moving, yes.
Mike: How far away is the Wanderers?
Mike: section.
David S. Kong: From where you are now, like, flying there directly would be, like, you know, 10 minutes or so, you know? How fast do dragon nets fly?
David S. Kong: 10-15 minute flight, like, you're… because you're closer to the center of the island right now, but if you, like, flat… if you flew, like, full speed, you could… you could fly across and, like…
Tim Sackton: So, totally fine for you to, like.
David S. Kong: Tummy tuck.
Tim Sackton: You can run however big you want, but it's supposed to be, like, 40 miles in diameter.
David S. Kong: So how long would it take for them to fly from, like, the edge of the temple to one of the.
Tim Sackton: Like, 20 miles? I mean…
David S. Kong: We can do soccer. How long would it… how long would it be?
Tim Sackton: Faye… I don't really know how fast dragonettes fly, that's… but… but, like, you know, hours… half a day?
Tim Sackton: Yeah, like, 20 miles… like, they're not flying 20 miles an hour. Maybe they're flying 20 miles an hour.
David S. Kong: Let's call it, you could get there in, like, an hour or two. Like, you call it, like, you could get there in, like, an hour.
Mike: Yeah.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Little Tony will call it, guys, come on up, huddle up, huddle up, we gotta figure this out, we gotta figure this out, and he'll sort of pause and hover in the air in one spot.
Tim Sackton: What are you… You both are flying around weirdly, but in the same sort of weird way.
Eric Rosenbaum: Ugh, yeah, we're trying to… we're trying to figure out what's going on here, which way it's coming from.
Tim Sackton: What's coming from?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Well, the…
Eric Rosenbaum: the blank.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Masai.
Eric Rosenbaum: it's… No, no, no, it's the…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): No, no, no, it's…
Mike: I'm just okay.
Eric Rosenbaum: go.
Mike: Kay that.
Mike: We look around, like, is there… Is there anything up here?
David S. Kong: Right now, you're just hovering kind of, like, up above the…
Mike: I'm gonna go up above them and just, like, look around, like, did anything… Do I… do I…
David S. Kong: You don't, you don't, I mean, again, you, you don't see anything, there's nothing obvious, but Zeno and, and,
David S. Kong: Lil Tony, like, again, there is, like, a directionality, like, there is, like, you're kind of realizing.
Mike: Which direction?
David S. Kong: Like, certain… Are you… it's a little tiny and z…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, yeah, yeah
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): So we're sort of, like, comparing notes, so I'm… I'm just trying to, like, kind of show with my hands, like, I think it's… I think that it's this way, right? I'm gonna look over to…
Eric Rosenbaum: It's the same, right?
David S. Kong: It is the same. It is the same.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah, same thing.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And this must…
Tim Sackton: Put it that way, then.
David S. Kong: Are you… are you gesturing? Like, kind of pointing?
Tim Sackton: assume this from the festival? Yeah, what are.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): What are you pointing towards?
David S. Kong: You're pointing directly at the Wanderer statue.
Mike: Like, something happened there.
Mike: We should go.
Tim Sackton: Let's go!
Eric Rosenbaum: Let's go.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Let's do it!
Eric Rosenbaum: Towards the humming, everybody?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, deeper into the silence, like, like Zeno said.
David S. Kong: So, okay. So, you all bolt off. You take off.
David S. Kong: Leaving the noise and the cacophony of the, festival behind you.
David S. Kong: As you.
David S. Kong: Start flying as quickly as you can, towards the Wanderer Statue.
David S. Kong: And… As you fly, And get closer and closer, and it's a, you know, it's a reasonably clear night.
David S. Kong: You notice as you're getting closer, to the statue, and, you know, you're kind of triangulating now, you're getting a feel for, like, okay, it's getting, you know, kind of stronger and, you know, kind of louder and or…
David S. Kong: Like, louder and more silent simultaneously for both of you, like, as you're getting closer to the statue.
David S. Kong: And you definitely can tell and feel that it's… there's some kind of, like…
David S. Kong: you're… you're drawn towards the palm of the wanderer. There's definitely… it feels like that is… is… the place.
David S. Kong: And, as you approach, you notice… you see, like, something glowing in the distance.
David S. Kong: In the palm of the wanderer.
David S. Kong: Right now, you're still, like, you know, 100 feet away or whatever, so you can see it, but it's, it's,
David S. Kong: But there's something, like, glowing, and it looks like it's hovering, like, above the palm.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, that looks interesting. Don't you guys live here?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah…
Eric Rosenbaum: to respond.
Eric Rosenbaum: -Oh. That's not your low thing?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: No, man.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Woo.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): What is that?
Eric Rosenbaum: Kinda looks like a butt. No, I'm just kidding.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Hmm.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Everything looks like a boat when you've got butts on the brain, I mean, it's… I get it.
Eric Rosenbaum: And you're still mourning your loss, I know, my apology.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That's not the end of the story for me and Ed.
David S. Kong: Ow!
Mike: How big is it?
David S. Kong: Looking, looking at it, like, just kind of your, your sense of the size of the palm and then the, the, the object itself, like, it looks pretty big. Like, it looks like…
David S. Kong: you know, 10 feet or more. Like, the glow is, like, quite large.
Mike: But it's not moving, right?
David S. Kong: It's not moving. It's not moving, it's just hovering over the palm.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah, I'm… I continue to think of, anecdotes I can make use of in routines later, so I will fly up to,
Eric Rosenbaum: Look down on it from above.
Eric Rosenbaum: Like, 20 feet over it.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, I'm gonna… I'm gonna stick close next to… Zeno.
David S. Kong: So y'all are gonna prep… you're gonna prep?
Tim Sackton: Loosen my… loosen my whip, in case I need to.
Tim Sackton: Pull it out.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Well, we know you can hit things with it.
David S. Kong: So, so as you're
David S. Kong: getting closer, you know, like, just describe, like, your speed as you're getting closer to the hand. Are you accelerating, keeping a steady pace? Like, what's your… how are you approaching the hand?
Eric Rosenbaum: I wanna, like, buzz over it at a meet… at, like, a moderate speed.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And I want to, like, buzz a sort of fly-by and around, like, circle at a moderate.
Tim Sackton: I'm gonna stay flanking on Zeno's wing.
Eric Rosenbaum: Nice.
David S. Kong: And, Sculpt, how about you?
Mike: I'll, approach, like…
Mike: Approached sort of more slowly, a little bit behind everybody else, but keeping a sharp eye on, like, whether it's reacting or what it might be doing.
David S. Kong: Okay. As you start to get closer,
David S. Kong: As you start to get closer, the light starts to dim from
David S. Kong: So you're probably, like, around 100 feet away, and then as you're getting closer and closer and closer, it starts to dim.
David S. Kong: And then, as you get closer and closer.
David S. Kong: Suddenly, the… whatever brightness there was around it.
David S. Kong: It goes completely dark, it kind of just fades out to, like, a completely dark…
David S. Kong: There's still an object there of some kind.
David S. Kong: And as also as you get closer and as the light fades away.
David S. Kong: Will Tony, you, and, Zeno?
David S. Kong: Little Tony, for you, it's, like, almost like a perfect, like, as the light fades out.
David S. Kong: For you, all of a sudden, the objects start to return, and everything kind of comes back to normal. And similarly for you, Zeno, like, as the light fades out, all of a sudden, for you, the tone, that beautiful tone that was in your head, also goes away.
Eric Rosenbaum: Seems like the light was making that beautiful sound.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Exactly, everything quiet, like you said.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Nope.
Tim Sackton: I'll land next to it.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
Tim Sackton: quake.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Same, yeah.
David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: As you land on the palm, You're looking at
David S. Kong: what looks like a huge egg. It's, it's like a… it's like a giant, like, yeah. It looks like, like, you know, again, the palm is dark, the whole area around here, you know, you're up super, super high up, and it's dark and windy.
David S. Kong: But the egg, it's like a larger oval, and there's these engravings in it as well, but everything is still, like, dark right now. Like, it's no longer lit, like what you saw from before, but it looks like there are these different etchings that are forming these, like, really interesting patterns, like, all around the outside of this egg.
David S. Kong: But it's silent.
Tim Sackton: I'll summon a Spectral Hand.
Tim Sackton: It'll drift over to the side and knock, knock.
Eric Rosenbaum: I didn't know you could do that.
David S. Kong: Usually…
Tim Sackton: Usually it's invisible.
David S. Kong: If you spectral hand knock, is that just, like, a regular hand knocking? Yeah. Or, like, what's that?
Tim Sackton: It's a mage hand.
David S. Kong: Yeah, you knock on it, you're… the mage hand… It feels,
David S. Kong: it feels not, like, totally metallic. It's definitely, like, not stone or wood, and it's not also… it's, like, something between stone and wood… it's something between, like, stone and metal. It's not, like, a totally, like, you know… but it's the material of it and the type of knocking, because, you know, you're draggingettes, y'all fucking love shiny shit and, like, knocking on things.
David S. Kong: It is not like any material that you have ever knocked on before. Like, it is something… the material itself sounds totally fucking different than any other material on this island that you've ever interacted with.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That's awesome! Can I… can I grab a little piece of it? What can I…
David S. Kong: There's no pieces. It's, like, completely smooth. It's completely smooth, except for these… these engravings that are… that are all kind of etched into the side of it.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Hmm…
Tim Sackton: I'll walk up to you. Wait, do you touch it?
Tim Sackton: Poke it with my whip.
David S. Kong: Sadget?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yes.
David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: When you touch it.
David S. Kong: It's hard to describe, but, like, the actual sensation when the kind of tip of your claw goes and touches the edge of this… this, you know.
David S. Kong: Metal object, this egg, whatever, whatever it's made out of.
David S. Kong: There's something about it… That, for you, feels…
David S. Kong: good. Like, there's something that, like, as you touch it, there's kind of a sense of, like.
David S. Kong: Peace and a sense of… Just, like…
David S. Kong: You feel… you feel warm inside, and something about it, like, feels…
David S. Kong: You know, there isn't quite a word that hits you, it's, like, on the tip of your tongue, like, what it feels like.
David S. Kong: You know, you feel… Like, warm and good inside, touching it.
David S. Kong: What is everybody else doing?
Mike: You said there's a bunch of etchings on it?
David S. Kong: Yeah.
Mike: Are they, like… Writing?
Mike: Are they designed?
David S. Kong: Yeah, it's design. It's, like, geometric design, but, like.
David S. Kong: Are you… do you want to do, investigation perception check?
Mike: Investigator.
Mike: Yeah, or perception. I mean, I'm looking to try and understand, like, the patterns, or the, like…
David S. Kong: Yeah, investigation. Make an investigation, Sean.
Mike: 21.
David S. Kong: Yeah, as you're looking at these etchings, because you kind of get up close to it, and by the way, too, when you touch the egg, or do you touch it, or do you just kind of look.
Mike: No, just looking at it.
David S. Kong: As you're looking at it, again, similarly, the patterns, like.
David S. Kong: there's clearly, like, a geometry. It's not, like, arbitrary, like, squiggly lines. It's like, oh, these are…
David S. Kong: like, sacred geometries. Like, these are definitely, like, patterns that…
David S. Kong: On this island, the only place that you've seen, kind of, patterns that look like this are, like.
David S. Kong: you know, the island's in ruins, you know what I mean? All of the different structures and things like that are in ruins. But there are places on the island still, and you know, these pilgrimage paths, these old roads, and things like that. But there are definitely spots, like, near the temple, near the ruins of the temple, and other places near these, you know, statues and so on as well.
David S. Kong: Where you've seen similar types of
David S. Kong: not necessarily these exact same shapes, but similar types of shapes. Like, you know, dragonettes don't draw, like, perfect, you know, per se, like, perfect geometric patterns, but this is, like, a perfect set of geometric patterns.
Tim Sackton: So… I'm gonna walk over to it.
Tim Sackton: Look at everybody else. That's a mechanical egg, right? It must open somehow. I'm gonna start, like…
Eric Rosenbaum: Wait! And Zeno says, hang on, don't try to open it.
Tim Sackton: Why not?
Eric Rosenbaum: I have this… I have this ability I can use… I usually use this to…
Eric Rosenbaum: Try to listen in to the mind of my rap battle opponent.
Eric Rosenbaum: to get whatever clever rhyme they're about to use, so I can use it first. It's very useful for that, but I think if there's a creature in there, I might be able to tell if it's thinking.
Eric Rosenbaum: This is Detect Thoughts.
David S. Kong: Nice.
Eric Rosenbaum: So it has a sense thoughts. You sense the presence of thoughts within 30 feet of yourself, belong to creatures that know languages or are telepathic.
Eric Rosenbaum: You don't read the thoughts, but you know the thinking creatures. There are spells blocked by one foot of stone, dirt, or wood, one inch of metal, or a thin sheet of lead.
Eric Rosenbaum: So I cast Detect Thoughts.
David S. Kong: Is there a die roll, like, associated with this? Or just, like, it just works?
Mike: The tech start's just the tech spots.
Tim Sackton: It just works unless you try and, like…
Mike: Unless you try and probe something.
Tim Sackton: scan deeply into what the… the creature is what I'm thinking.
David S. Kong: You do not detect any thoughts.
Tim Sackton: See? Let me try and open it.
Eric Rosenbaum: Wait, maybe it's… maybe it's gonna try to run. Just kidding. Yeah, go ahead.
Tim Sackton: Maybe this metal's messing up, maybe this shell is messing up your spell.
Tim Sackton: Gonna, like, poke around and see if there's, like, a latch or, like, a thin… even if it's just a thin seam that I can find. Just, like, tap on it at a few places with the edge of my whip.
David S. Kong: Investigation.
Tim Sackton: 15! It's getting higher!
Eric Rosenbaum: Alright, get it?
David S. Kong: Fire?
Eric Rosenbaum: abandoned.
David S. Kong: You're definitely, like, getting into it in terms of trying to, like, you know, find a weak spot, and it's very… you're doing a studious study. Like, this is, like, a rigorous, like, proper study. You do not find any.
Mike: Is this?
David S. Kong: To open this.
Mike: I don't know…
David S. Kong: What's that?
Mike: No, go ahead.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I want to use my, thing-talking talent.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Where, a couple times a day, I can talk to things, so I'm gonna reach out, I'm gonna put my hand on the side of it. Not, like, exploring it, but, like, put it in on the shoulder of a friend and be like, listen, buddy, I know I… I don't know you, you don't know me, this can feel a little awkward, especially if you're in a new place you've never been before, but I…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): This is one of my spots, I love to hang out here. Welcome, it's great to have you here, and what's, what's your deal, buddy? What brings you here?
David S. Kong: Is there a role associated with this as well? Or is this just you just…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I think as we talked about it, it is a just get to have the conversation. It doesn't give me any particular advantage or any information, it just allows me to have the conversation with the thing.
David S. Kong: Roll a D20, anyways.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Meh.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Do you want me to roll, like, a Persuasion or something, or just a…
David S. Kong: Just, just roll straight D20, and I'm just looking for something above 10.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Here's just a straight roll. It's a 13…
David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: You're kind of doing your persuasive, you know, talk, and your, you know, your usual chatter with objects, and…
David S. Kong: Like, as you kind of… and what's your… what's your position to the.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I think I'm standing with my back to the island.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Like, my back's sort of on the island side, so my front, as I imagine the egg, is between… sort of between me and the ocean, and I'm standing on the hand, like, putting my hand on it in front of it.
David S. Kong: Oh, so you're touching the egg?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
David S. Kong: As you touch the egg, Another… again, like, you feel, just as you touch it, this, like.
David S. Kong: Warmth in your hand.
David S. Kong: like, a warmth in your body. You know, to the extent that, like, dragonettes have, like, little hairs, you know, and hair on their scales and on their, you know, their fur or whatever.
David S. Kong: They… it kind of, like, stands up, like, in a wave, like, going down your hand.
David S. Kong: And as you talk to the egg, and, you know, kind of say, like, hey, you know, what's your deal, da-da-da-da.
David S. Kong: You hear a word in your mind that captures to you
David S. Kong: At the tip of your tongue, like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: this feeling.
David S. Kong: That had been… been missing, that you've been trying to kind of find this whole time?
David S. Kong: And… The word that comes into your mind is home.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I'll say it out loud in response.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): H-O-M-E HOME.
David S. Kong: HOME home.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Boom.
Eric Rosenbaum: What you talking about?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Welcome, welcome! I… I think the egg says home.
Eric Rosenbaum: I need to get home?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Whoa!
Tim Sackton: Or is it home?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Welcome home, buddy, and I'm gonna give it, like, a big hug.
David S. Kong: Aw, man.
Eric Rosenbaum: I don't know, man, I think he's trying to get home.
David S. Kong: You give it a hug?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
David S. Kong: Schwartz, or Lil' Tony, like… When you hug the egg.
David S. Kong: And you're… are you, like, genuinely, with real sincerity, being like, welcome home? Yeah.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, yeah, yeah.
David S. Kong: When you hug the egg, You feel… Something… so…
David S. Kong: Sacred. And something so beautiful come over your entire system.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And…
David S. Kong: It's… I mean, it's… It's hard to describe this in anything other than…
David S. Kong: Like, a religious sense of, like, hey, you are moved
David S. Kong: In the most profound way that you have ever been moved.
David S. Kong: And… That embrace and the sincerity behind that embrace, and your expression of home to the egg.
David S. Kong: You find that you are… you're just… there's… there are tears coming down your face, and…
David S. Kong: There's a connection to you of…
David S. Kong: The feelings… all of the feelings of home that you've ever had.
David S. Kong: Like, with your clutchmates, with your parents, with your loved ones.
David S. Kong: And it's like all of those moments of home that you've ever felt.
David S. Kong: are all, like, merged into this one feeling that you have right now with this egg. And that's just one layer of home.
David S. Kong: There's something else beneath it that is so much deeper, like a deeper, deeper feeling of home than you've ever, ever experienced before, as you huggedly say.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Wow, that's beautiful. I'm gonna sort of let go of the embrace and just, like, sit back down. She's like, wow, man.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Wow, mother.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Y'all should hug this egg.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Mmm.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Hmm.
Eric Rosenbaum: It is a beautiful pebble-like object, little Tony, but we gotta figure out what it's here for.
Eric Rosenbaum: Why was it growing?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): debut.
Eric Rosenbaum: Why is it humming?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): It's the most beautiful pebble I've ever seen.
Tim Sackton: A little big to call it a pebble.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Peanut.
Eric Rosenbaum: I'm just trying to speak little Tony's language, you know?
David S. Kong: So wait, who else has touched it?
David S. Kong: Just, Jazzina?
David S. Kong: Or, only, only, Lil' Tunny? Who else has touched it?
Tim Sackton: Well, I mean, I…
Eric Rosenbaum: Was poking at it.
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: So you're poking at it with a tool, though, right?
Tim Sackton: I mean, I was, like, trying to find seams and things, I think I would have touched it. Not… I'm not, like, hugging it or anything.
David S. Kong: Yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay, so just for you as well, like, when you… anytime that you actually touched it yourself, like, but not with a tool.
David S. Kong: You also felt this, like…
David S. Kong: you felt moved. Like, you felt like, oh, shit, like, you know? Dragonettes are usually, like, you know, fun, like, talking shit and all that type of stuff, but, like, there was, like, a… there was… it's… again, it… there's very few moments in, like, Dragonette life and culture where you feel that sense of move… being moved, but you felt it when you touched it.
Tim Sackton: I'm gonna… So, Huskas?
Tim Sackton: And I, like, step over towards it.
Tim Sackton: I'm gonna kind of nuzzle my head against it.
Tim Sackton: And sort of put a hand on it and say, What do you need, buddy?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Come on.
Tim Sackton: tell us.
David S. Kong: And you're… you're… you're also in a very, very… oh, and Schwartz, okay, I should have added this, my bad.
David S. Kong: When you hugged it and it told you home.
David S. Kong: The traces near where you were, like, hugging it.
David S. Kong: started to just glow. And, like, the slightest little hum of light started to come, like, as you…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Come over, everybody hug it, like, all the way around it, like, it's so big, like, it… everybody give it a hug at once. All the way around.
Eric Rosenbaum: I hope Zeno follows his lead.
Eric Rosenbaum: Can we, like, sculpt.
David S. Kong: I know you're real sad, we're almost done.
David S. Kong: We're almost back.
Mike: Alright, I'm fine.
David S. Kong: You're good You're good, you're good.
Mike: Right.
David S. Kong: Did you guys all go and hug the egg?
Mike: Sure, yes.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: So, as you all go, and it's weirdly, like, kind of perfectly sized for all of you.
David S. Kong: To be hugging this egg.
David S. Kong: And as you reach your claws and kind of, like, reach around, and it's kind of like a sweet moment, you know? You're, like, all hugging this egg, you know, and then also, it's like, we'll have to make a, you know, chat GPT image of this later. But, like, you're all hugging the egg, and your claws are, like, kind of…
David S. Kong: and you're… and, you know, you've had a day. Like, this has been, like, a really pretty fucking awesome day for your squad. And now…
Tim Sackton: Some of our squad.
David S. Kong: Well, even for you, you've had some redemption.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Highlights and low lows.
David S. Kong: As you all hug the egg.
David S. Kong: The patterns on the egg begin to glow, and all of you experience, again, this…
David S. Kong: it's hard to describe it other than, like, the most sacred experience you've ever had in your lives. Like, this is, like, this is, like, a very, very powerful, sacred moment.
David S. Kong: And as you touch it, the egg… begins to…
Eric Rosenbaum: Whoa.
David S. Kong: glow.
David S. Kong: And light up.
David S. Kong: And these 8 points of light start to appear across the egg.
David S. Kong: As all of you are touching it, Holding it.
David S. Kong: And just feeling this deep, deep sense of being moved.
David S. Kong: Bye.
David S. Kong: This embrace of each other, but then also the embrace of the egg.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And as you touch it, and as it lights up.
David S. Kong: you feel also, in some weird way, that your consciousness is merging together. Like, you're hugging it as kind of, like, four distinct entities, but the longer you hug it, the more that it feels like you're actually just one entity.
David S. Kong: And as you transition Into this feeling of, oh, shit.
David S. Kong: You know, we're not for things, but we're actually one thing.
David S. Kong: Your consciousness starts to fade and shift.
David S. Kong: And… Where once you were sitting on the palm of a wander holding an egg, You're no longer sitting…
David S. Kong: And the wanderer, and holding the palm of an egg.
David S. Kong: You're someplace else now.
David S. Kong: You're feeling something… But it's actually… Darkness.
David S. Kong: And it's something you haven't felt in a very, very long time, if ever.
David S. Kong: And a sense of despair.
David S. Kong: In a sense… That there's no hope.
David S. Kong: A sense that…
David S. Kong: Whatever good was in the world, and whatever was light, and whatever was shining, and bright, and laughter, and family.
David S. Kong: This is… The opposite of that.
David S. Kong: This is dark. This is despair.
David S. Kong: And you're starting to see now, stretched out, this night sky.
David S. Kong: With the skies on fire.
David S. Kong: And it's burning.
David S. Kong: Raging fire.
David S. Kong: Deep, deep, dark fire.
David S. Kong: There's still a few points of light in the sky.
David S. Kong: But you can see them slowly going out, one by one.
David S. Kong: By one, as you watch.
David S. Kong: And as you get closer, you realize that there's a figure on the ground.
David S. Kong: Lying on the ground.
David S. Kong: And as you get closer and closer, collectively, all of you kind of getting closer to this scene.
David S. Kong: He realized that, lying on the ground, There's a dragonette there.
David S. Kong: And the dragonette.
David S. Kong: is… broken.
David S. Kong: is… Wounded severely.
David S. Kong: And it's a… it's a purple dragon net.
David S. Kong: It's an older one.
David S. Kong: You've never seen this one before, huh
David S. Kong: But it's got some, you know, silvery fur, and it's got some… Amethyst-looking skin and scales.
David S. Kong: But one of its wings is folded back on itself.
David S. Kong: broken.
David S. Kong: And it's lying in a pool of blood.
David S. Kong: Deep, deep, dark blood.
David S. Kong: And as you get closer to this dragonette, You realize it's dying.
David S. Kong: And not only is it dying, it's, like, gonna die.
David S. Kong: Very, very soon, that these are his lost breaths.
David S. Kong: And as you get closer now.
David S. Kong: You're now inside the dragon egg.
David S. Kong: You're… you are the dragon head, and you are dying.
David S. Kong: And you're experiencing the last gasps and breaths.
David S. Kong: And as you, the lying… as you, the dragonette, lying on the ground, dying, looking at the sky and fire, and these lights going out.
David S. Kong: You can see in the distance.
David S. Kong: small little sparks start to fly out of the sky. These little… these bright points are going up, but then these streaks of light are flying around. And you see one of these streaks of light flying closer and closer and closer to you. And you know you're gonna die soon. You know any moment this could be your last breath.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: But…
David S. Kong: As it gets closer, you feel to yourself a little bit of, I need to stay alive, at least to see what this light is.
David S. Kong: And the light gets closer and closer, and closer and brighter, and brighter and brighter.
David S. Kong: And finally, The light comes, and it consumes you completely.
David S. Kong: And you are no longer the Dragonette.
David S. Kong: You are no longer whatever you were.
David S. Kong: But you feel as that light touches you.
David S. Kong: this word in your head, and this sensation, because it's a beautiful sensation. It's just like the sacred sensation you just felt hugging the egg together, holding each other.
David S. Kong: When there's a word.
David S. Kong: That echoes in your collective mind's eye.
David S. Kong: And it's home.
David S. Kong: And you feel as this light
David S. Kong: envelops you, and this feeling of home envelops you. Suddenly, these images start to appear.
David S. Kong: And it's images of…
David S. Kong: A man with a jade hand, and you're feeling like getting yourself getting scratched on the chin, oh, you fucking love this, getting scratched on the chin so much, this is, like, the best shit ever.
David S. Kong: You feel yourself getting scratched on the belly. You're like, oh, this is the, like, the best shit ever.
David S. Kong: And you see other figures, too. Other friends, other beings that you've called family, and have felt the sensation of home.
David S. Kong: You see… An island.
David S. Kong: And you see a perfectly circular island.
David S. Kong: And you see all of these other dragon ants flying around, and the clutches, and the eggs, and this deep, deep sense that this is home.
David S. Kong: And… as…
David S. Kong: you get closer to the island. Now you're traveling there. You actually feel that you are flying through the air.
David S. Kong: And before… sorry, as you're experiencing these images of home.
David S. Kong: You travel through a space of just… unimaginable…
David S. Kong: geometry, and it's… you can't even talk about it as, like, a physical place. But just light, energy, patterns… you feel an incredible force as you're moving through this.
David S. Kong: And then… You come out.
David S. Kong: And you see, before you.
David S. Kong: This sea, this vast, vast sea in this night sky. And you're hurtling towards that sea, over the sea, and then you see a storm in the distance, this weird, like, vertical storm that's just, like, hovering.
David S. Kong: And then you crash into the storm.
David S. Kong: It's silent inside the storm.
David S. Kong: And then finally, you get closer and see these 8 statues and the Wanderer's Palm.
David S. Kong: And you land, and you crash into that statue.
David S. Kong: And as you now… who were once Ford, Dragonettes, and then one Dragonette, and then… the light.
David S. Kong: You now merge back into… This space and into this egg.
David S. Kong: And the four of you… wake up.
David S. Kong: And you're lying on the ground.
David S. Kong: Next to this dragon egg, or next to this glowing egg.
David S. Kong: And all of the lights from the egg, as you awake up from this set of visions.
David S. Kong: Slowly start to fade.
David S. Kong: And darken.
David S. Kong: And the egg itself goes dark.
David S. Kong: And as the egg goes dark, each of you starts to experience something.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Difference.
David S. Kong: Little Tony?
David S. Kong: As you're lying there on your back, just kind of…
David S. Kong: just however you can, processing whatever the fuck just happened. You start experiencing something, and this has been a day. Your normal shit, and then all of a sudden you can't hear everything, you can hear everything back again, like, what the hell's going on?
David S. Kong: You notice as you start to expand your consciousness out, because normally the palm is completely quiet, and it is quiet, and you expand your consciousness down to the, you know, the wrist and down the arm.
David S. Kong: And your usual friends that you see along the way, they start talking to you like normal.
David S. Kong: But you feel, just like you did earlier, that suddenly you feel like you can tune it. You feel like you can talk to any rock that you want.
David S. Kong: You feel like any rock, you can tune it and turn this one off, turn that one off. And as you expand outwards, you realize, as you expand outward from beyond the wanderer and the statue.
David S. Kong: That you can now talk and engage with every single object.
David S. Kong: That you are scanning across the entire island, as far as you start going and expanding outwards. And it's, like, ultra-fucking-high resolution, like, any object, I can talk to this one or not. I can listen to this one or not.
David S. Kong: You've never experienced anything even close to this magnitude.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Crystal…
David S. Kong: Perception and resolution.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Zeno…
David S. Kong: As you're lying there, and coming to that perfect note that you heard in your head earlier, you start to hear in your head not just one note, but a chord.
David S. Kong: But not just a chord, even.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It…
David S. Kong: Feels somehow, like.
David S. Kong: A set of notes combined together, playing something that's so resonant and beautiful, yes to Dragon S. But you realize that you can kind of assemble these notes into any pattern that you want.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And you…
David S. Kong: You somehow have this sensation that the notes that you're arranging in your mind
David S. Kong: They will be beautiful for the trees. They could be beautiful for…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The river.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: for the animals.
David S. Kong: Even… there feels like, for you, there's some combination of notes in your mind that the wind blow up.
David S. Kong: And as you're kind of just playing with this, you also notice that each note
David S. Kong: You thought that there was a note, but actually that note is made up of even more notes. It's like there are sub-tones within a tone.
David S. Kong: And you find that as you're making these compositions in your mind, the sub-tones create new layers and new density and complexity of music that you have never before imagined or thought of before in your mind. And somehow you can arrange it, and somehow you know that the notes and the chords that you're making
David S. Kong: are fucking sick. Like, whoever's gonna be listening to this is like, this is the most sacred shit they've ever heard in their lives. Esca, as you're lying there, and feeling…
David S. Kong: Similarly to everybody else, what the fuck is going on?
David S. Kong: You noticed in your body, and in your being.
David S. Kong: You're a hunter, you're an acrobat, you've got incredible control over your body and what you can do.
David S. Kong: And yet, somehow, now, It's almost as though every muscle in your body
David S. Kong: You have some kind of precise control over.
David S. Kong: You are able to take…
David S. Kong: The sinew of a muscle on your finger, and activate it and control it with total perfection.
David S. Kong: The little strand of muscle on your leg below your knee, your hunting muscles, all of them are activated, again, with a precision and a power that you've never felt before.
David S. Kong: And… you know how you felt when you killed that and hunted that king crab? How you felt on that day, and that was a perfect day, that was your perfect hunt? This…
David S. Kong: feels like you could go and hunt a thousand of those crags. This feels like you could find the most hidden, darkest, strongest beast in the ocean, and go hunt that shit.
David S. Kong: It's a level of, like, power and confidence that you have never felt before. And, mike…
David S. Kong: For Sculpit, as you're lying there.
David S. Kong: You, your whole life, have had this feeling around magic, and a feeling that there's certain ways in which you just couldn't control this. You want to, you know, be able to do something, but there's this wild energy that's flowing within you that you can't quite keep a lid on.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: But now for you…
David S. Kong: Just like before, you were able to kind of teleport, like, 10, 20 feet, you're feeling now as though…
David S. Kong: All of that wildness is completely tamed. You have complete precision and control over how you want to move it. If you want it to go 1 feet, 10 feet, 30 feet, 50 feet.
David S. Kong: It all feels completely easy. It all feels…
David S. Kong: novice. Something that would be so simple for you to do.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And so somehow.
David S. Kong: You've been searching for this wildness to finally be tamed.
David S. Kong: And it is completely a slave to whatever you want.
David S. Kong: And as all of you are experiencing these things in your bodies, in your systems, for maybe, like, you know, a couple of minutes.
David S. Kong: they disappear.
David S. Kong: And they're gone.
David S. Kong: And as you lay there, contemplating…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: However each of you are contemplating.
David S. Kong: Whatever this experience was, whatever that vision was, and whatever was coursing through your bodies.
David S. Kong: The camera kind of zooms out.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: to the statue of the Wanderer.
David S. Kong: Palm, and this now…
David S. Kong: Darkened egg that has now settled down back onto the ground, and it's just lifeless and animate.
David S. Kong: And unmistakably, as the camera kind of pans around the wanderer.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You see…
David S. Kong: The Eye of the Wanderer.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The eye light up blue and bright.
David S. Kong: And we'll stop there.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): So cool.
Mike: Sounds good.
Eric Rosenbaum: I think we're going from here. Wow, I like it. That was so fun, Kong. That was a great session.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That was awesome.
Mike: Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: How you feeling, Don?
David S. Kong: I feel great. That was super fun.
Tim Sackton: Awesome.
Mike: Yeah.
Mike: What do you guys think of?
David S. Kong: going on?
Mike: I need to read the session notes, I have no idea. Oh, no.
Tim Sackton: You can't ask players that right at the end of the session.
David S. Kong: Tim knows too much, but anyways…
Tim Sackton: I know too much.
David S. Kong: But, but anyways, that was super fun, guys. I've never, I think the last time I DM'd was, was in high school. Like, we did, like, a session in my basement, like, I DM'd something.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, you definitely DM'd in high school.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah.
Tim Sackton: And middle school, too.
David S. Kong: Like, once or twice, maybe.
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: But,
David S. Kong: That was… that was, yeah, that was fun. Hope you guys enjoyed that.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, it was awesome.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That was super fun.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): It's like…
Tim Sackton: Sometimes it's more fun to roll low than to roll high.
David S. Kong: God.
Eric Rosenbaum: Dude, that was the best. 100% agree.
David S. Kong: That was the fucking best, dude. That, like, that series of roles was so good.
Eric Rosenbaum: It just makes the story so much more interesting. Yeah, it's so perfect. Chaotic, yeah.
David S. Kong: Perfect.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I learned…
David S. Kong: What were you gonna.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): like, Dragonetti all four of the characters are. Like, like, we took the… like, what Dimitar was pointing to without just, like, imitating.
Mike: Yeah.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): What he's doing, or… like, it's really, like, building out that part of the world in a way that's so, so fun.
Eric Rosenbaum: Another view is that they are quite…
Eric Rosenbaum: Pathological, each in their own unique ways.
David S. Kong: Superfather.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh, yes.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh my god, yeah, your stuff was really funny tonight, Fortz, I was really appreciating that.
David S. Kong: Well, I mean, so much of it was improvised. Oh, you gotta go for it, Mike.
Mike: I just have to go to bed. This was really fun, but I'm, like, asleep, so…
David S. Kong: Well, just…
Mike: play again in a week, so I'll.
David S. Kong: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
David S. Kong: Just, but just, what I was gonna say, Eric,
David S. Kong: the… the… all of the, like, the Dragonette, like, slice of Life stuff was actually… a lot of that was… was improv… like, I had some idea of the scenes, but it was pretty improvised, but the
David S. Kong: The role-playing was so good. Like, you guys killed that shit. It was so fun, like, just all of the different… the dynamics of the characters, and just, it was, like, really, like… like, that is, like, the most I've, like, laughed in a session. Like, it was, like, properly hilarious for, like.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah.
David S. Kong: It was, like, you guys were really, like, locked in on the Dragonet energy, and I actually had no idea how that was gonna go, but it was, like, very, like, I don't know, Xena was, like, a, for me, was, like, a fun, like, I don't know, it was, like, I just kind of made it up, like… like, I knew going into it that that would be a fun character, but that, just, like, the whole beginning was, like, a very fun, like.
David S. Kong: unpredictable roleplay that ended up, like.
David S. Kong: I don't know, it was great. Like, I thought y'all… just how you all role-played was so fun. It was really, really great.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): It was such a… like, it was a very organic, all-of-the-characters-coming-together sort of thing, and then, like, giving us, like, such a strong personality foil to sort of react to and play off against.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, it's…
Eric Rosenbaum: That's a good technique, yeah, that's true.
Tim Sackton: It's… When you commit to the bit, it gets all the players to commit, too.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yes, right? Yes.
Eric Rosenbaum: Right. But there's… and there was, like, high stakes, but it was fairly brief in terms of, like, oh, it's this performance, then it's over. It's nice.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, it moved in a really, really, like.
Eric Rosenbaum: Hmm.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I was impressed with how you moved the pieces of that along. And, like, you broke us off and brought us back together again, like, it didn't feel.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, that's like… that's like advanced DMing.